<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 09:15:03 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter Cards</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Introduction With Twitter Cards, you can attach rich photos, videos and media experience to Tweets that drive traffic to your website. Simply add a few lines of HTML to your webpage, and users who Tweet links to your content will have a "Card" added to the Tweet that’s visible...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>App Installs and Deep-Linking</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/app-installs-and-deep-linking</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Introduction One of the most important features in the new Cards is the ability to let users to download your app (if the user doesn't already have it installed), or deep-link into your own app (if the app is already installed on the user's mobile device). You can enable app...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Summary Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/summary-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Summary Card can be used for many kinds of web content, from blog posts and news articles, to products and restaurants. It is designed to give the reader a preview of the content before clicking through to your website. The Tweet below from the United Nations (@UN) shows a Summary Card (...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Summary Card with Large Image</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/large-image-summary-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Summary Card with Large Image features a large, full-width prominent image alongside a tweet. It is designed to give the reader a rich photo experience, and clicking on the image brings the user to your website. The Tweet below from @TechCrunch shows a Summary Card with Large Image along...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Cards Markup Tag Reference</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/markup-reference</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The table in this section explains the OpenGraph fallback behavior for each Twitter tag. Overview of all Twitter Card Tags Property Card Value OpenGraph Fallback twitter:card all summary,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Getting Started Guide</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/getting-started</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Getting Started with Cards Card and Content Attribution URL Crawling &amp; Caching Multiple URLs in a Tweet Twitter Cards and Open Graph Getting Started with Cards To get started with implementing the Cards markup, you'll want to specify the type of card for your content by adding...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Server to Server Network Support</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/server-server-network-support</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub provides Server to Server integrations with the following networks: &nbsp; Jumptap &nbsp; InMobi &nbsp; MobFox &nbsp; Tapit &nbsp; Mojiva&nbsp; &nbsp; Huntmads &nbsp; This means that there is no additional development work required. Once you have created an account with a...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Create and Manage a Segment (Ad Networks)</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/create-and-manage-segment-ad-networks</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Segments Overview MoPub&rsquo;s network management interface allows you to group your inventory into &ldquo;segments&rdquo;. A &ldquo;segment&rdquo; is a slice of your inventory with specific apps or ad units that can be targeted to specific countries and networks. It is a combination of three...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>AdMob Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/admob-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Note: If you are using the updated version of AdMob, please follow the instructions at this link instead: http://help.mopub.com/customer/portal/articles/1376821-updating-admob-revenue-reporting In order to set up AdMob for ad network revenue reporting:&nbsp;You will need to enter your AdMob...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Millennial InMobi Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/millennial-inmobi-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Ad network revenue reporting allows you to view important metrics from your networks directly in MoPub. Learn more about ad network revenue reporting here. Revenue reporting requires the Millennial Username, Password. Your app name must also exactly match the app name in your Millennial dashboard....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>InMobi Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/inmobi-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[We&rsquo;ve recently updated revenue reporting for InMobi to reflect InMobi&rsquo;s latest API. &nbsp;If you previously set up MoPub revenue reporting for InMobi, you need to contact InMobi and update your InMobi information on MoPub to ensure your reports continue to work. Important Notes:...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Embedded Timelines</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/embedded-timelines</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Overview Embeddable timelines make it easy to syndicate any public Twitter timeline to your website with one line of code. Create an embedded timeline from your widgets settings page on twitter.com, or choose “Embed this…” from the options menu on profile, search and collection...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>iAd Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/iad-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub offers ad network revenue reporting for ad networks that offer a third party API to provide you with more accurate ad performance data.&nbsp; In order to set up ad network revenue reporting for iAd, you will need to enter your iTunes Connect username and password onto your iAd Network...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>GET statuses/lookup</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/get/statuses/lookup</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Returns fully-hydrated tweet objects for up to 100 tweets per request, as specified by comma-separated values passed to the id parameter. This method is especially useful to get the details (hydrate) a collection of Tweet IDs. GET statuses/show/:id is used to retrieve a single tweet object.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Huntmads Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/huntmads-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Ad network revenue reporting allows you to view important metrics from your networks directly in MoPub. Learn more about ad network revenue reporting here. In order to set up ad network revenue reporting for Huntmads, you will need to enter your Huntmads API Token&nbsp;&nbsp;on the network setup...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Issues with AdMob &amp; Proguard</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/issues-admob-proguard</link>
   <description><![CDATA[&nbsp; If you are using Proguard and the Admob the adapter is included but the AdMob SDK is getting stripped out, then when a call is made to that ad network, an application error will occur. &nbsp; In your configuration file of proguard (proguard.cfg), simply add this line: &nbsp; # AdMob...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Orders &amp; Line Items FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/orders-line-items-faq</link>
   <description><![CDATA[My line item is currently paused and I would like to set it live. When I do so, the line item remains in the paused state.What is going on? Please check the status of the order to which the line item belongs, and ensure that the order is set live. The order level supersedes the line...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Chartboost Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/chartboost-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[In order to set up revenue reporting for Chartboost, you need to first set up Chartboost as a network. Directions to set up Chartboost. In order to set up Chartboost for revenue reporting, you will need to enter in your Chartboost User ID and Chartboost User Signature into the MoPub UI. The User...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Chartboost Network Setup</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/chartboost-network-setup</link>
   <description><![CDATA[In order to set up Chartboost, you will need the most recent MoPub SDKs for iOS and Android. iOS: https://github.com/mopub/mopub-ios-sdk/ Android: https://github.com/mopub/mopub-android-sdk/ 1. You will first need to integrate the Chartboost SDK and Chartboost supporting files for ad serving to...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Ad Network Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ad-network-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub allows you to view your ad network revenue, impression, and click data, all in one place. From the MoPub interface you can get a snapshot of how your ad networks have been performing, allowing you to manage and optimize your revenue more efficiently. Sounds great, how do I get started? To...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
