<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 02:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>Certified Products</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/programs/twitter-certified-products/products</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Certified Products Product Description Badge Adobe Social Adobe Social connects the dots between social interactions and business results, enabling marketers to demonstrate social impact at every stage of the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Player Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/player-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Player Card type requires special approval, and is not available for immediate approval at this time. The Player Card is for streaming media experiences such as audio, video, or slideshows, and allows you to present your content inside of an iframe within the Tweet. Unlike the photo and...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Troubleshooting &amp; FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/troubleshooting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[We created this troubleshooting guide to help you identify and resolve commonly encountered issues during Cards development. We've tried to make this guide as useful and comprehensive as possible. If there's something wrong, or you feel something should be added, please reach out to us via the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Player Card Whitelisting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/player-card/whitelisting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Thank you for your interest in using the Twitter Player Card. To help expedite the whitelisting of your Card, it is useful to read the below fully and provide the appropriate information. Unfortunately, we are currently backlogged in our approval of Player Cards, so responses may vary...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Follow Button</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/follow-button</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Follow Button is a small widget which allows users to easily follow a Twitter account from any webpage. The Follow Button uses the same implementation model as the Tweet Button, and its integration is just as simple. By using the Follow Button, you agree to the Developer Rules of the Road....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Entities in Twitter Objects</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/entities</link>
   <description><![CDATA[See also Entities from the Field Guide. Entities for Tweets Entities for Retweets Entities for Users Entities for Direct Messages Entities for Tweets Entities provide structured data from Tweets including resolved URLs, media, hashtags and mentions without having to parse the text to...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Entities</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/platform-objects/entities</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Entities provide metadata and additional contextual information about content posted on Twitter. Entities are never divorced from the content they describe. In API v1.1, entities will be returned wherever Tweets are found in the API. Entities are instrumental in resolving URLs. Read Entities in...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Calendar of API changes</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/calendar</link>
   <description><![CDATA[This page lists important upcoming dates for consumers of Twitter's APIs. The dates listed will be as specific as possible, but may not be exact for various reasons. Please continue to follow @twitterapi and the Twitter developer blog for announcements about the platform. Upcoming changes...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST account/update_profile_banner</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/account/update_profile_banner</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Uploads a profile banner on behalf of the authenticating user. For best results, upload an]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST account/update_profile_background_image</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1/post/account/update_profile_background_image</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Updates the authenticating user's profile background image. This method can also be used to enable or disable the profile background image. Although each parameter is marked as optional, at least one of image, tile or use must be provided when making this request.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST blocks/create</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/blocks/create</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Blocks the specified user from following the authenticating user. In addition the blocked user will not show in the authenticating users mentions or timeline (unless retweeted by another user). If a follow or friend relationship exists it is destroyed.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Streaming API keyword matching</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/streaming-apis/keyword-matching</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The way POST statuses/filter checks if a tweet includes a keyword is already explained in the track parameter documentation but explaining how every corner case works would make it look more complicated than it is, so on this page you can try interactively. Caution: This was written to be as close...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST geo/place</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/geo/place</link>
   <description><![CDATA[As of December 2nd, 2013, this endpoint is deprecated and retired and no longer functions. Place creation was used infrequently by third party applications and is generally no longer supported on Twitter. Requests will return with status 410 (Gone) with error code 251. Follow the discussion about...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Which languages are supported by embedded widgets?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/faq/#23735</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Widgets are available in 28 of the languages supported by Twitter's website and clients. The language is determined automatically from the page a widget is embedded upon: That is, an HTML lang attribute on the embed code element or an ancestor determines the language of the widget chrome. Ideally...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>What happens if twitter.com has an error or is over capacity?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/faq/#23736</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Tweet Button and Follow Button are hosted on high performance content distribution networks, and are separate from twitter.com. This means if twitter.com goes down your site will not be affected, and the button will still display. When a user clicks the button, the Tweet or User Intent is...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Which browsers do Twitter for Websites widgets support?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/faq/#23733</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Twitter for Websites widgets are tested and supported in most popular browsers. Browsers which are fully supported are: Chrome 4 Firefox 4 Safari 5 Opera 10 Internet Explorer 8 Mobile Safari 5 Android 4 Other, older browsers—such as Internet Explorer 7, Firefox 3, and Android 2.x—are partially...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>App Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/app-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[App Card is a great way to better represent mobile applications on Twitter and to drive installs. We designed the App Card to allow for a name, description and icon, and also to highlight attributes such as the rating and the price. This will require adding some new markup tags to your pages,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Photo Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/photo-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Photo Card puts the image front and center in the Tweet: Web Mobile To define a photo card experience, set your card type to "photo" and provide a twitter:image. Twitter...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Summary Card with Large Image</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/large-image-summary-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[In addition to our regular Summary Card, we also have a format that allows you to feature a larger image above the title and description of the Card. The regular Summary Card features a thumbnail image in the upper right hand corner of the Card, but if you want to more prominently feature your...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Cards Markup Tag Reference</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/markup-reference</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The table in this section explains the OpenGraph fallback behavior for each Twitter tag. Overview of all Twitter Card Tags Property Card Value OpenGraph Fallback twitter:card all summary,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
