<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2014 02:15:03 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>Simple Ads Demo - iOS (2/3): Testing a Specific Ad Unit</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/simple-ads-demo-ios-23-testing-specific-ad-unit</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Testing a specific Ad Unit - iOS: &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;1)&nbsp;Retrieve&nbsp;the ad unit ID that you want to test.&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;a)&nbsp;Click on &lsquo;Code Integration&rsquo; button to display your ad unit id &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Simple Ads Demo - Android (3/3): Testing JavaScript/MRAID Ad Tags</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/simple-ads-demo-android-33-testing-javascriptmraid-ad-tags</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Testing JavaScript/MRAID Ad Tags create a new Order - &lsquo;TestOrder1&rsquo; within TestOrder1 create a new line item - &lsquo;TestLineItem1&rsquo; when creating TestLineItem1, be sure to target your desired test AdUnit (recommended to create a new AdUnit - &lsquo;...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Simple Ads Demo - Android (2/3): Testing a Specific Ad Unit</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/simple-ads-demo-android-23-testing-specific-ad-unit</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Testing a specific Ad Unit&nbsp; Pull the Ad Unit ID that you want to test Click on &lsquo;Code Integration&rsquo; button&nbsp;and the ad unit ID will be shown in the new window Copy the ad unit displayed &nbsp; Open SimpleAdsDemo in Eclipse navigate to...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Simple Ads Demo - Android (1/3): Opening in Eclipse</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/simple-ads-demo-android-13-opening-eclipse</link>
   <description><![CDATA[​This is the first help article in the &#39;Simple Ads Demo - Android&#39; series. This series will walk you through the process of setting up MoPub&#39;s Simple Ads Demo application on your computer/device as well as guide you through 3rd party (AdMob/Millennial) SDK integration. This will enable...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Simple Ads Demo - iOS (3/3): Testing JavaScript/MRAID Ad Tags</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/simple-ads-demo-ios-33-testing-javascriptmraid-ad-tags</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Testing JavaScript/MRAID Ad Tags Create a new order - &lsquo;TestOrder1&rsquo;​ Within TestOrder1 create a new Line Item - &lsquo;TestLineItem1&rsquo; When configuring this new Line ItemTestLineItem1, ensure that the AdUnit you intend on testing is properly targeted&nbsp;(It is highly...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Simple Ads Demo - iOS (1/3): Opening in Xcode</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/simple-ads-demo-ios-13-opening-xcode</link>
   <description><![CDATA[This is the first help article in the &#39;Simple Ads Demo - iOS&#39; series. This series will walk you through the process of setting up MoPub&#39;s Simple Ads Demo application on your computer/device. This will enable you to quickly test various creatives, ad units and network settings in a live...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Video</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-video</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Video ads offer a valuable opportunity to drive more revenue for your interstitial inventory. &nbsp;MoPub enables you to automatically introduce video ads from MoPub Marketplace demand partners without burdening your app with additional SDKs. Our video ad support is built to give you the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Refresh Rates</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/refresh-rates</link>
   <description><![CDATA[When you create an ad unit, you will need to set the refresh rate. The refresh rate is the number of seconds until the next ad unit displays. For example, if you set a refresh rate of 30 seconds, the second ad unit will display 30 seconds later...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Reporting Categories and Metrics Descriptions</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/reporting-categories-and-metrics-descriptions</link>
   <description><![CDATA[When running a report, you can report on six categories and include desired metrics. The following are categories on which you can report: App Ad Unit Priority Line Item Type Order Line Item Creative Month Week Day Hour Country OS iOS Device For example, if you wanted to report on a single Line...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Forecasting for Direct Ads</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/forecasting-direct-ads</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Overview of Forecasting MoPub’s Forecasting feature allows you to quickly evaluate available impressions based on the inventory that’s already been booked and sold. As shown below, Forecasting allows you to visualize available inventory, and see the value of each Guaranteed Line Item. This...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Location and Keyword Data Passing</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/location-and-keyword-data-passing</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Data passing allows for more relevant and targeted ad content to be displayed to the user. Currently MoPub is able to allow for location and keyword data to be passed. Location Passing Android will automatically pass over Latitude and Longitude coordinates if available Keywords Passing You can...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>How To Integrate Facebook Audience Network Using Custom Events</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/how-integrate-facebook-audience-network-using-custom-events-0</link>
   <description><![CDATA[You can work with Facebook's Audience Network using Custom Events the same way you can with other ad network on MoPub. MoPub's pre-built Custom Event adapter makes this process even simpler. For more information on Custom Events, see Ad Network Setup.Important Note: These Custom Events are...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Checking the MoPub SDK Version</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/checking-mopub-sdk-version</link>
   <description><![CDATA[As a best practice, we recommend that you update to the most recent version of the MoPub SDK every time you push an update to the Apple App Store or Google Play Store. To check the version of the SDK that is currently integrated in your application, you can look at the MoPub.java file for Android...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Technical Integration FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/technical-integration-faq</link>
   <description><![CDATA[I’m testing my ad unit and nothing is happening. Why? At the moment, ad units that aren't receiving ad requests from live traffic get removed from our ad servers periodically. When the ad unit starts receiving traffic again, the information gets loaded on those machines and there's a short delay...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>AdMarvel Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/admarvel-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[When using the AdMarvel SDK, passing IFA and AndroidID can dramatically affect Marketplace performance. For iOS: AdMarvel SDK version 3.0.1 or higher is required to pass IDFA and&nbsp;work correctly with Marketplace. For Android: All versions of the AdMarvel SDK pass AndroidID and are&nbsp;...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Setting Up Conversion Tracking</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/setting-conversion-tracking</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Conversion tracking is used to properly measure the effectiveness of cross-promotions and direct sold advertisements. &nbsp;Therefore, we recommend that publishers always implement conversion tracking. The conversion tracking network event only happens once-- a file is stored on device so that the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Orders &amp; Line Items Setup</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/orders-line-items-setup</link>
   <description><![CDATA[An Order is a set of Line Items, usually created for an ad campaign. The Order targets one or more Ad Units to display creatives After logging into app.mopub.com, go to your ‘Orders’ tab. Click on the ‘Add a New Order’ button at the top right. Name your Order, drop in the Advertiser, and add a...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Orders &amp; Line Items Settings</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/orders-line-items-settings</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Within MoPub’s dashboard, Orders &amp; Line Item settings can be adjusted on different ad sources for a particular ad unit. Line item types include: Guaranteed (G), Network (N), MoPub Marketplace (M), Promotional (P), Non-Guaranteed (NG), or Backfill Promotional (B). More information on Line Item...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Orders &amp; Line Items FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/orders-line-items-faq</link>
   <description><![CDATA[My line item is currently paused and I would like to set it live. When I do so, the line item remains in the paused state.What is going on? Please check the status of the order to which the line item belongs, and ensure that the order is set live. The order level supersedes the line item level, so...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Order &amp; Line Item Types</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/order-line-item-types</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Order Types There are four campaign types that MoPub supports to help with creating ad serving strategies. MoPub prioritizes Orders in the following sequence: guaranteed, promotional, networks, Marketplace, and then backfill promotional. Within each category of Orders, CPM is used to prioritize....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
