<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 03:45:02 +0100</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>Obtaining access tokens</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/auth/obtaining-access-tokens</link>
   <description><![CDATA[In order to make authorized calls to Twitter's APIs, your application must first obtain an OAuth access token on behalf of a Twitter user or you could issue Application-only authenticated requests when user context is not required. The way you will obtain such tokens will depend on your use case...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Single-user OAuth with Examples</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/auth/oauth/single-user-with-examples</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Please note: Most developers will find working with Application-only authentication a superior approach than what is documented below. Twitter offers the ability for you to retrieve a single access token (complete with oauth_token_secret) from application detail pages found on dev.twitter.com....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter Card Analytics</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/analytics</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Introduction Twitter Cards allow you to attach rich media experiences to Tweets about your content; Twitter Card analytics gives you related insights into how your content is being shared on Twitter. Through personalized data and best practices,Twitter Card analytics reveals how you can...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter Cards</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Introduction Twitter Cards make it possible for you to attach media experiences to Tweets that link to your content. Simply add a few lines of HTML to your webpages, and users who Tweet links to your content will have a "card" added to the Tweet that’s visible to all of their followers....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>User Profile Images and Banners</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/user-profile-images-and-banners</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Profile Images Profile images (or avatars) are an important component of a Twitter account's expression of identity. To upload an avatar on behalf of a user, use POST account/update_profile_image. Alternative image sizes for user profile images You can obtain a user's most recent profile image,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Troubleshooting &amp; FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/troubleshooting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[We created this troubleshooting guide to help you identify and resolve commonly encountered issues during Cards development. We've tried to make this guide as useful and comprehensive as possible. If there's something wrong, or you feel something should be added, please reach out to us via the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter Libraries</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/twitter-libraries</link>
   <description><![CDATA[These libraries, while not necessarily tested by Twitter, should support Twitter API v1.1. Want your library to be included in this index or need to update the details we have? Submit your library for inclusion! Libraries built and maintained by Twitter Java hbc &mdash; A Java HTTP client for...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Calendar of API changes</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/calendar</link>
   <description><![CDATA[This page lists important upcoming dates for consumers of Twitter's APIs. The dates listed will be as specific as possible, but may not be exact for various reasons. Please continue to follow @twitterapi and the Twitter developer blog for announcements about the platform. Upcoming changes...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Certified Products</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/programs/twitter-certified-products/products</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Certified Products Product Description Badge Adobe Social Adobe Social connects the dots between social interactions and business results, enabling marketers to demonstrate social impact at every stage of the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Player Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/player-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Player Card type requires special approval, and is not available for immediate approval at this time. The Player Card is for streaming media experiences such as audio, video, or slideshows, and allows you to present your content inside of an iframe within the Tweet. Unlike the photo and...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Player Card Whitelisting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/player-card/whitelisting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Thank you for your interest in using the Twitter Player Card. To help expedite the whitelisting of your Card, it is useful to read the below fully and provide the appropriate information. Unfortunately, we are currently backlogged in our approval of Player Cards, so responses may vary...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Follow Button</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/follow-button</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Follow Button is a small widget which allows users to easily follow a Twitter account from any webpage. The Follow Button uses the same implementation model as the Tweet Button, and its integration is just as simple. By using the Follow Button, you agree to the Developer Rules of the Road....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Entities in Twitter Objects</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/entities</link>
   <description><![CDATA[See also Entities from the Field Guide. Entities for Tweets Entities for Retweets Entities for Users Entities for Direct Messages Entities for Tweets Entities provide structured data from Tweets including resolved URLs, media, hashtags and mentions without having to parse the text to...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Entities</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/platform-objects/entities</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Entities provide metadata and additional contextual information about content posted on Twitter. Entities are never divorced from the content they describe. In API v1.1, entities will be returned wherever Tweets are found in the API. Entities are instrumental in resolving URLs. Read Entities in...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST account/update_profile_banner</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/account/update_profile_banner</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Uploads a profile banner on behalf of the authenticating user. For best results, upload an]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST account/update_profile_background_image</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1/post/account/update_profile_background_image</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Updates the authenticating user's profile background image. This method can also be used to enable or disable the profile background image. Although each parameter is marked as optional, at least one of image, tile or use must be provided when making this request.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST blocks/create</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/blocks/create</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Blocks the specified user from following the authenticating user. In addition the blocked user will not show in the authenticating users mentions or timeline (unless retweeted by another user). If a follow or friend relationship exists it is destroyed.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Streaming API keyword matching</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/streaming-apis/keyword-matching</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The way POST statuses/filter checks if a tweet includes a keyword is already explained in the track parameter documentation but explaining how every corner case works would make it look more complicated than it is, so on this page you can try interactively. Caution: This was written to be as close...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST geo/place</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/geo/place</link>
   <description><![CDATA[As of December 2nd, 2013, this endpoint is deprecated and retired and no longer functions. Place creation was used infrequently by third party applications and is generally no longer supported on Twitter. Requests will return with status 410 (Gone) with error code 251. Follow the discussion about...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Which languages are supported by embedded widgets?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/faq/#23735</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Widgets are available in 28 of the languages supported by Twitter's website and clients. The language is determined automatically from the page a widget is embedded upon: That is, an HTML lang attribute on the embed code element or an ancestor determines the language of the widget chrome. Ideally...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
