<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 00:15:04 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>Getting Started Guide</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/getting-started</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Getting Started with Cards Card and Content Attribution URL Crawling &amp; Caching Multiple URLs in a Tweet Twitter Cards and Open Graph Getting Started with Cards To get started with implementing the Cards markup, you'll want to specify the type of card for your content by adding...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>App Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/app-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The App Card is a great way to represent mobile applications on Twitter and to drive installs. We designed the App Card to allow for a name, description and icon, and also to highlight attributes such as the rating and the price. The Tweet below from Jason Stark (@jaysonst) shows an App Card (...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Gallery Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/gallery-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Gallery Card allows you to represent collections of photos within a Tweet. This Card type is designed to let the user know that there's more than just a single image at the URL shared, but rather a gallery of related images. The Tweet below from @VisitCA shows a Gallery Card below the 140...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Photo Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/photo-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Photo Card puts the image front and center in the Tweet. Clicking on the photo expands it to a richer, detailed view. Below is a tweet from @Flickr showcasing the Photo Card. Stunning photo of mountainous landscape and reflections http://t.co/esvsXTy7Tq&mdash; Flickr (@Flickr) January 15,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Summary Card with Large Image</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/large-image-summary-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Summary Card with Large Image features a large, full-width prominent image alongside a tweet. It is designed to give the reader a rich photo experience, and clicking on the image brings the user to your website. The Tweet below from @Yahoo shows a Summary Card with Large Image along with...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Summary Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/summary-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Summary Card can be used for many kinds of web content, from blog posts and news articles, to products and restaurants. It is designed to give the reader a preview of the content before clicking through to your website. The Tweet below from the United Nations (@UN) shows a Summary Card (...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Product Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/product-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Product Card is a great way to represent product and retail items on Twitter. This Card type is designed to showcase your products via an image, a description, and allow you to highlight two other key details about your product. The Tweet below from @iHeartRadio shows a Photo Card below...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>CMS Integration Guide</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/twitter-cards-for-cms-wordpress-blogger-tumblr</link>
   <description><![CDATA[This page has tips for integrating Twitter Cards into popular CMS systems like Wordpress, Tumblr and Blogger. If you have feedback or additional references we should add, please tell us in the forums. Thanks! Wordpress Site, Self-Hosted or Third-Party Hosted Jetpack Plugin JM Twitter Cards...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>App Installs and Deep-Linking</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/app-installs-and-deep-linking</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Introduction One of the most important features in the new Cards is the ability to allow users to download your app (if the user doesn't already have it installed), or deep-link into your own app (if the app is already installed on the user's mobile device). The ability to enable...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Player Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/player-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Video clips and audio streams have a special place on the Twitter platform thanks to the Player Card. By implementing a few HTML meta tags to your website and following the Twitter Rules of the Road, you can deliver your rich media to users across the globe. Player Card...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter Cards</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Introduction With Twitter Cards, you can attach rich photos, videos and media experience to Tweets that drive traffic to your website. Simply add a few lines of HTML to your webpage, and users who Tweet links to your content will have a "Card" added to the Tweet that’s visible...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter Card Analytics</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/analytics</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Introduction Twitter Cards allow you to attach rich media experiences to Tweets about your content; Twitter Card analytics gives you related insights into how your content is being shared on Twitter. Through personalized data and best practices,Twitter Card analytics reveals how you can...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>GET lists/memberships</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/get/lists/memberships</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Returns the lists the specified user has been added to. If user_id or screen_name are not provided the memberships for the authenticating user are returned.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST statuses/update_with_media</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/statuses/update_with_media</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Updates the authenticating user's current status and attaches media for upload. In other words, it creates a Tweet with a picture attached. Unlike POST statuses/update, this method expects raw multipart data. Your POST request's Content-Type should be set to multipart/form-data with the media[]...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>GET search/tweets</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/get/search/tweets</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Returns a collection of relevant Tweets matching a specified query. Please note that Twitter's search service and, by extension, the Search API is not meant to be an exhaustive source of Tweets. Not all Tweets will be indexed or made available via the search interface. In API v1.1, the response...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Set-up Twitter for Websites</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/tfw/set-up</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The easiest way to create a Twitter for Websites widget—a Tweet button, Follow button, embedded Tweet or timeline—is to use our configuration tools, then copy and paste the generated HTML code into the template for your site. Create a Tweet or Follow Button Create an Embedded Timeline (note,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST statuses/update</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1/post/statuses/update</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Updates the authenticating user's status, also known as tweeting. To upload an image to accompany the tweet, use POST statuses/update_with_media. For each update attempt, the update text is compared with the authenticating user's recent tweets. Any attempt that would result in duplication will be...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>GET help/configuration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/get/help/configuration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Returns the current configuration used by Twitter including twitter.com slugs which are not usernames, maximum photo resolutions, and t.co URL lengths. It is recommended applications request this endpoint when they are loaded, but no more than once a day.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>GET statuses/lookup</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/get/statuses/lookup</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Returns fully-hydrated tweet objects for up to 100 tweets per request, as specified by comma-separated values passed to the id parameter. This method is especially useful to get the details (hydrate) a collection of Tweet IDs. GET statuses/show/:id is used to retrieve a single tweet object.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST statuses/update</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/statuses/update</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Updates the authenticating user's current status, also known as tweeting. To upload an image to accompany the tweet, use POST statuses/update_with_media. For each update attempt, the update text is compared with the authenticating user's recent tweets. Any attempt that would result in duplication...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
