<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 22:00:04 +0100</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>Embedded Timelines</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/embedded-timelines</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Overview Embeddable timelines make it easy to syndicate any public Twitter timeline to your website with one line of code. Just like timelines on twitter.com, embeddable timelines are interactive and enable your visitors to reply, Retweet, and favorite Tweets directly from your...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Embedded Tweets</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/embedded-tweets</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Overview Embedded Tweets make it possible for you take any Tweet and embed it directly in to the content of your article or website. Tweets display with expanded media like photos, videos, and article summaries, and also include real-time retweet and favorite counts. When...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Follow Button</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/follow-button</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Follow Button is a small widget which allows users to easily follow a Twitter account from any webpage. The Follow Button uses the same implementation model as the Tweet Button, and its integration is just as simple. By using the Follow Button, you agree to the Developer Rules of the Road....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Web Intents</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/intents</link>
   <description><![CDATA[By using Web Intents, you agree to the Developer Rules of the Road. Make it easy to bring interactivity to Tweets that you display on the web. Web Intents provide popup-optimized flows for working with Tweets &amp; Twitter Users: Tweet, Reply, Retweet, Favorite, and Follow. They make it possible...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Share Bookmarklet</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/share-bookmarklet</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Overview The Share Bookmarklet makes it easy for you to share any webpage on Twitter, even if there isn&rsquo;t a Tweet Button. It works in all major browsers and is easy to install. Getting the Bookmarklet Share on Twitter To use the bookmarklet just drag the Share on Twitter...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>How should I file a bug report about a Twitter widget?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/faq/#25874</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Sorry that you're having trouble. We work constantly to fix bugs, tweak functionality and improve browser support of our widgets, and hopefully we can help resolve your issue, too. Before reporting a bug, please verify as much of the following as you are able: Check the FAQ for known limitations...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Why am I signed in as a different user on apps.twitter.com than on dev.twitter.com?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/faq/#25873</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Apps.twitter.com uses Twitter's centralized login and session service while dev.twitter.com does not currently share sessions with twitter.com.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>What happened to application management on dev.twitter.com?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/faq/#25872</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Application management has moved to https://apps.twiter.com/.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Where do I manage my Twitter applications?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/faq/#25871</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Manage your Twitter applications on https://apps.twiter.com by signing in with your Twitter account.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>CSS for Embedded Widgets</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/tfw/embed-code-css</link>
   <description><![CDATA[When embedding a Twitter for Websites widget, a placeholder is pasted into your page. This takes the form of either a link to the equivalent page on Twitter (a profile, timeline, or Web Intent), or an HTML &lt;blockquote&gt; of the Tweet being embedded. These shallow versions of the widgets are...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Why can&#039;t I create an application?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/faq/#25781</link>
   <description><![CDATA[If you're having trouble fulfilling application creation requirements, please contact our Platform Operations team by using the "I have an API policy question not covered by these points" option of the contact form at https://support.twitter.com/forms/platform]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter Cards</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Introduction Twitter Cards make it possible for you to attach media experiences to Tweets that link to your content. Simply add a few lines of HTML to your webpages, and users who Tweet links to your content will have a "card" added to the Tweet that’s visible to all of their followers....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Obtaining access tokens</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/auth/obtaining-access-tokens</link>
   <description><![CDATA[In order to make authorized calls to Twitter's APIs, your application must first obtain an OAuth access token on behalf of a Twitter user or you could issue Application-only authenticated requests when user context is not required. The way you will obtain such tokens will depend on your use case...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Single-user OAuth with Examples</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/auth/oauth/single-user-with-examples</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Please note: Most developers will find working with Application-only authentication a superior approach than what is documented below. Twitter offers the ability for you to retrieve a single access token (complete with oauth_token_secret) from application detail pages found on dev.twitter.com....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter Card Analytics</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/analytics</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Introduction Twitter Cards allow you to attach rich media experiences to Tweets about your content; Twitter Card analytics gives you related insights into how your content is being shared on Twitter. Through personalized data and best practices,Twitter Card analytics reveals how you can...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>User Profile Images and Banners</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/user-profile-images-and-banners</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Profile Images Profile images (or avatars) are an important component of a Twitter account's expression of identity. To upload an avatar on behalf of a user, use POST account/update_profile_image. Alternative image sizes for user profile images You can obtain a user's most recent profile image,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Troubleshooting &amp; FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/troubleshooting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[We created this troubleshooting guide to help you identify and resolve commonly encountered issues during Cards development. We've tried to make this guide as useful and comprehensive as possible. If there's something wrong, or you feel something should be added, please reach out to us via the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter Libraries</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/twitter-libraries</link>
   <description><![CDATA[These libraries, while not necessarily tested by Twitter, should support Twitter API v1.1. Want your library to be included in this index or need to update the details we have? Submit your library for inclusion! Libraries built and maintained by Twitter Java hbc &mdash; A Java HTTP client for...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Calendar of API changes</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/calendar</link>
   <description><![CDATA[This page lists important upcoming dates for consumers of Twitter's APIs. The dates listed will be as specific as possible, but may not be exact for various reasons. Please continue to follow @twitterapi and the Twitter developer blog for announcements about the platform. Upcoming changes...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Certified Products</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/programs/twitter-certified-products/products</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Certified Products Product Description Badge Adobe Social Adobe Social connects the dots between social interactions and business results, enabling marketers to demonstrate social impact at every stage of the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
