<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 16:45:02 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>MRAID Vendor Tag Certification Process</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mraid-vendor-tag-certification-process</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub MRAID Vendor Certification Process Guiding Principles: The MoPub SDK is built to be fully compliant with the IAB MRAID v1.0 specification Overview: Pre-Certification Questionnaire Setup Vendor Self Test Vendor impression test Reporting test Scale Test Best Practices...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Best Practices</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-best-practices</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Why enable Marketplace? MoPub Marketplace is our real-time bidding exchange, which gives publishers access to an additional revenue source through a competitive auction with complete transparency and control. MoPub’s...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Custom Native Network Setup</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/custom-native-network-setup</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub supports 3rd party Ad Network SDKs through a Custom Native Network implementation. If an Ad Network not listed provides their solution through an SDK, the network may be integrated leveraging MoPub’s Custom Events. The integration of Custom Native Networks requires the development...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Ad Network Setup</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ad-network-setup</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub allows for the set-up and management of multiple Ad Networks through the MoPub Dashboard. Ad Networks will serve ads to the ad unit ID that is referenced. From within the dashboard, click the Networks tab. From your Network tab, click “Add a Network” MoPub...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>What is MoPub?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/what-mopub</link>
   <description><![CDATA[What is MoPub? MoPub is a mobile ad serving platform. We help you monetize your apps more effectively. We offer a free, self-serve product that lets you get started with ad serving quickly while offering sophisticated features that you will need as you grow. With streamlined campaign management,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Japanese Pages</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/ja-pages</link>
   <description><![CDATA[アプリケーション・インストールとディープ・リンク Twitterカード トラブルシューティング＆FAQ Playerカード Twitter公認製品プログラム 開発者向けの表示要件 埋め込みタイムライン 埋め込みツイート ツイートボタン]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Scripting: Events</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/tfw/events</link>
   <description><![CDATA[By using Twitter Javascript, you agree to the Developer Rules of the Road. By default, widgets-js will find mark-up in a page and convert basic, functional mark-up into rich interactive widgets. In addition, there are a number of functions of widgets-js that allow developers to work with Twitter...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Technical Integration FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/technical-integration-faq</link>
   <description><![CDATA[I&rsquo;m testing my ad unit and nothing is happening. Why? At the moment, ad units that aren&#39;t receiving ad requests from live traffic get removed from our ad servers periodically. When the ad unit starts receiving traffic again, the information gets loaded on those machines and there&#39;s a...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>How To Integrate Facebook Audience Network Using Custom Events</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/how-integrate-facebook-audience-network-using-custom-events-0</link>
   <description><![CDATA[You can work with Facebook&#39;s Audience Network using Custom Events the same way you can with other ad network on MoPub. MoPub&#39;s pre-built Custom Event adapter makes this process even simpler. For more information on Custom Events, see Setting Up Ad Networks. Important Note: These Custom...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Server to Server Network Support</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/server-server-network-support</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub provides Server to Server integrations with the following networks: &nbsp; Jumptap &nbsp; InMobi &nbsp; MobFox &nbsp; Tapit &nbsp; Mojiva&nbsp; &nbsp; Huntmads &nbsp; This means that there is no additional development work required. Once you have created an account with a...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Ad Networks FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ad-networks-faq</link>
   <description><![CDATA[What networks does MoPub support? MoPub supports dozens of the most popular ad networks via server-to-server connections. For a list of standard supported networks, visit here.&nbsp;In addition to these networks, you can set up any network on MoPub via a &quot;Custom Event&quot;.&nbsp;These...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>MoPub Macros</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mopub-macros</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub supports the following macros for a publisher&rsquo;s 3rd party ad tags and trackers: &nbsp; Click URL (Unescaped): &nbsp;%%CLICK_URL_UNESC%%&nbsp; &nbsp; Click URL (Escaped): &nbsp;%%CLICK_URL_ESC%% &nbsp; Cache Buster (Generates a random number): %%CACHEBUSTER%% &nbsp; Ad...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>AdMarvel Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/admarvel-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[AdMarvel SDK When using the AdMarvel SDK, passing IFA and AndroidID can dramatically affect Marketplace performance. The versions below are certified to work correctly with Marketplace: iOS: AdMarvel SDK version 3.0.1 and higher is required to pass IDFA Android: All...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Checking the MoPub SDK Version</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/checking-mopub-sdk-version</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Checking the MoPub SDK Version As a best practice, we recommend that you update to the most recent version of the MoPub SDK every time you push an update to the Apple App Store or Google Play Store. To check the version of the SDK that is currently integrated in your...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The MoPub reporting tool can be found here or by clicking &lsquo;Reports&rsquo; under Your Account. &nbsp; Reports can be broken down using up to three different type of paramaters &nbsp; Please note that data for yesterday becomes available at 12:00PM Pacific Time &nbsp; You can...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Tweet Button parameter reference</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/tweet-button/reference</link>
   <description><![CDATA[A Tweet Button supports prepopulating share text, hashtags, and a Twitter account reference. Associate related Twitter accounts to drive followers. Tweet content parameters in_reply_to optional Status ID string of a parent Tweet such as a Tweet from your account (if applicable). Example...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter | MoPub Server-to-Server API Technical Specifications 1.0</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/twitter-mopub-server-server-api-technical-specifications-10</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Overview The MoPub Server-to-Server API makes it easier for ad networks and demand partners to connect with the MoPub platform outside of SDK libraries. To integrate with MoPub through the Server-to-Server API, follow the integration approval process and technical specifications...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Generating Ad Unit Code for Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/generating-ad-unit-code-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[From the Ad Unit page, you can pull the ad unit code by clicking &ldquo;Code Integration&rdquo;. Once all your ad units have been created, you can follow our technical guide to begin integration of the SDK. &nbsp;]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Embedded Tweet parameter reference</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/embedded-tweets/reference</link>
   <description><![CDATA[An Embedded Tweet supports customization in data-* attributes and JavaScript factory functions. This reference document describes parameters used in all formats. Reference the oEmbed API to set these parameters as part of an HTML response for a Tweet ID or URL. Parameters id required The...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Create an Ad Unit</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/create-ad-unit</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Your application will require one or more Ad Units in order to show ads. From your Inventory tab, click “Add a New App” Select your platform choice in the Device Format section Select Ad Format type...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
