<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 15:45:03 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>MRAID Vendor Tag Certification Process</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mraid-vendor-tag-certification-process</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub MRAID Vendor Certification Process Guiding Principles: The MoPub SDK is built to be fully compliant with the IAB MRAID v1.0 specification Overview: Pre-Certification Questionnaire Setup Vendor Self Test Vendor impression test Reporting test Scale Test Best Practices...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>How to Add Users to Your Account</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/how-add-users-your-account</link>
   <description><![CDATA[You can add users in different roles to your MoPub account. What does this mean? Multiple Users: Users can use their individual logins to access the same account Roles and Permissions: Users can have different roles (e.g. Admin,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter | MoPub Server-to-Server API Technical Specifications 1.0</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/twitter-mopub-server-server-api-technical-specifications-10</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Overview The MoPub Server-to-Server API makes it easier for ad networks and demand partners to connect with the MoPub platform outside of SDK libraries. To integrate with MoPub through the Server-to-Server API, follow the integration approval process and technical specifications...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Embedded Tweet CMS best practices</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/embedded-tweets/cms</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Overview An Embedded Tweets adds pieces of the global conversation happening on Twitter to your site, content, and commentary. Sites powered by a CMS or custom software can provide deeper integration with Twitter content through site-level display preferences, content macros for cross-...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter for Websites</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/tfw</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Twitter for Websites is a suite of embeddable widgets and client-side scripting tools to integrate Twitter and display Tweets in your site or web app. You can find documentation for publishers and developers here, refer to the Twitter for Websites FAQ, or ask questions or share what you...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Website implementation checklist</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/web/best-practices</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Overview Websites can improve content distribution, build an audience, and help viewers navigate to their best content views by including Twitter-specific markup and buttons in their pages. Connect your content with the Twitter audience. Set context with link previews Attribute content to...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>AdMob Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/admob-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[In order to set up AdMob for ad network revenue reporting: You will need to enter your AdMob Username, the AdMob API password and the AdMob API key. 1. Username This is the username that you use to log in to AdMob 2. API Password AdMob requires an API password to...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>How do I obtain an API key?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/faq/#7447</link>
   <description><![CDATA[You can create an application record (which includes an API key) by navigating to https://apps.twitter.com/ Most integrations with the API will require you to identify your application to Twitter by way of an API key. On the Twitter platform, the term "API key" usually refers to what's called an...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter for Websites FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/tfw/faq</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Which browsers does the Tweet Button support? Does the Tweet Button support other languages? What are the dimensions of the Tweet Button? What happens if twitter.com has an error or is over capacity? I want to use multiple Tweet Buttons on my page. Is there anything I should know? Can I...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Mobile Web Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mobile-web-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub supports a simple Javascript tag to integrate our ad serving technology into your mobile websites. Simply include the following tags, customized with your ad unit ID and creative size. Details Paste the following code snippet into your mobile webpage where you'd like to see ads appear:...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Summary Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/summary-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Summary Card can be used for many kinds of web content, from blog posts and news articles, to products and restaurants. It is designed to give the reader a preview of the content before clicking through to your website. The Tweet below from the United Nations (@UN) shows a Summary Card (...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Native Direct Ad Serving</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/native-direct-ad-serving</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Native Direct Ad Serving The MoPub platform allows you to integrate ads from many different advertising sources, including MoPub Marketplace and direct ads. Below is a short guide for setting up your first direct sold native ad. Set Up Your Direct Campaign...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>How to Use the MoPub Dashboard</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/how-use-mopub-dashboard</link>
   <description><![CDATA[How to Use the MoPub Dashboard The MoPub Dashboard enables you to see your entire monetization strategy on a single screen. The Dashboard offers a single, comprehensive view of all your app revenue data -- including ad networks, MoPub Marketplace, and direct campaigns. With the Dashboard...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Self-Testing Your Creatives with the MoPub SDK and SimpleAdsDemo Sample App</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/self-testing-your-creatives-mopub-sdk-and-simpleadsdemo-sample-app</link>
   <description><![CDATA[This tutorial is a step-by-step guide that shows you how to self-test your creatives using the SimpleAds Demo app. Self Testing with the MoPub SDK and Simple Ads Demo App What: SimpleAds Demo is a mobile application for iOS and Android that demonstrates how live tags would render/behave on MoPub...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Setting Up Custom URIs</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/setting-custom-uris</link>
   <description><![CDATA[To have the click through of ads go to an in-app purchase, you&#39;ll need to set up a custom URI scheme like so:&nbsp;http://mobiledevelopertips.com/cocoa/launching-your-own-application-via-a-custom-url-scheme.html. Once you do that, all you have to do is drop the custom URI into the click through...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>MoPub OpenRTB 2.1 Specification</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/mopub/openrtb-21-specification</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Updated August 4,2014 1. Overview MoPub RTB is a way for DSPs and advertisers to bid on each ad impression where the winning bid will pay the second-highest price in the auction.  This protocol is largely based on the OpenRTB 2.1 specification.   Note that our adaptation may require certain...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Payments</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-payments</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The revenues and other data displayed in the Marketplace dashboard may be different than the final payment. &nbsp;There are several reasons for this. &nbsp;The values shown in the dashboard are based on real-time data feed. &nbsp;At the end of the processing period, MoPub will look at the actual...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Video</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-video</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Video ads offer a valuable opportunity to drive more revenue for your interstitial inventory. &nbsp;MoPub enables you to automatically introduce video ads from MoPub Marketplace demand partners without burdening your app with additional SDKs. Our video ad support is built to give you the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Simple Ads Demo - Android (3/3): Testing JavaScript/MRAID Ad Tags</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/simple-ads-demo-android-33-testing-javascriptmraid-ad-tags</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Testing JavaScript/MRAID Ad Tags create a new Order - &lsquo;TestOrder1&rsquo; within TestOrder1 create a new line item - &lsquo;TestLineItem1&rsquo; when creating TestLineItem1, be sure to target your desired test AdUnit (recommended to create a new AdUnit - &lsquo;...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Simple Ads Demo - Android (2/3): Testing a Specific Ad Unit</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/simple-ads-demo-android-23-testing-specific-ad-unit</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Testing a specific Ad Unit&nbsp; Pull the Ad Unit ID that you want to test Click on &lsquo;Code Integration&rsquo; button&nbsp;and the ad unit ID will be shown in the new window Copy the ad unit displayed &nbsp; Open SimpleAdsDemo in Eclipse navigate to...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
