<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 20:30:03 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>MoPub OpenRTB 2.1 Specification</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/mopub/openrtb-21-specification</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Updated August 4,2014 1. Overview MoPub RTB is a way for DSPs and advertisers to bid on each ad impression where the winning bid will pay the second-highest price in the auction.  This protocol is largely based on the OpenRTB 2.1 specification.   Note that our adaptation may require certain...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Payments</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-payments</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The revenues and other data displayed in the Marketplace dashboard may be different than the final payment. &nbsp;There are several reasons for this. &nbsp;The values shown in the dashboard are based on real-time data feed. &nbsp;At the end of the processing period, MoPub will look at the actual...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Video</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-video</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Video ads offer a valuable opportunity to drive more revenue for your interstitial inventory. &nbsp;MoPub enables you to automatically introduce video ads from MoPub Marketplace demand partners without burdening your app with additional SDKs. Our video ad support is built to give you the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Simple Ads Demo - Android (3/3): Testing JavaScript/MRAID Ad Tags</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/simple-ads-demo-android-33-testing-javascriptmraid-ad-tags</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Testing JavaScript/MRAID Ad Tags create a new Order - &lsquo;TestOrder1&rsquo; within TestOrder1 create a new line item - &lsquo;TestLineItem1&rsquo; when creating TestLineItem1, be sure to target your desired test AdUnit (recommended to create a new AdUnit - &lsquo;...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Simple Ads Demo - Android (2/3): Testing a Specific Ad Unit</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/simple-ads-demo-android-23-testing-specific-ad-unit</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Testing a specific Ad Unit&nbsp; Pull the Ad Unit ID that you want to test Click on &lsquo;Code Integration&rsquo; button&nbsp;and the ad unit ID will be shown in the new window Copy the ad unit displayed &nbsp; Open SimpleAdsDemo in Eclipse navigate to...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Simple Ads Demo - Android (1/3): Opening in Eclipse</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/simple-ads-demo-android-13-opening-eclipse</link>
   <description><![CDATA[​This is the first help article in the &#39;Simple Ads Demo - Android&#39; series. This series will walk you through the process of setting up MoPub&#39;s Simple Ads Demo application on your computer/device as well as guide you through 3rd party (AdMob/Millennial) SDK integration. This will enable...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Simple Ads Demo - iOS (3/3): Testing JavaScript/MRAID Ad Tags</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/simple-ads-demo-ios-33-testing-javascriptmraid-ad-tags</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Testing JavaScript/MRAID Ad Tags Create a new order - &lsquo;TestOrder1&rsquo;​ Within TestOrder1 create a new Line Item - &lsquo;TestLineItem1&rsquo; When configuring this new Line ItemTestLineItem1, ensure that the AdUnit you intend on testing is properly targeted&nbsp;(It is highly...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Simple Ads Demo - iOS (2/3): Testing a Specific Ad Unit</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/simple-ads-demo-ios-23-testing-specific-ad-unit</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Testing a specific Ad Unit - iOS: &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;1)&nbsp;Retrieve&nbsp;the ad unit ID that you want to test.&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;a)&nbsp;Click on &lsquo;Code Integration&rsquo; button to display your ad unit id &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; b...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Simple Ads Demo - iOS (1/3): Opening in Xcode</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/simple-ads-demo-ios-13-opening-xcode</link>
   <description><![CDATA[This is the first help article in the &#39;Simple Ads Demo - iOS&#39; series. This series will walk you through the process of setting up MoPub&#39;s Simple Ads Demo application on your computer/device. This will enable you to quickly test various creatives, ad units and network settings in a live...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>How to Create a Direct Native Ads Campaign</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/how-create-direct-native-ads-campaign</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Create an Ad Unit for your native ad &nbsp; Typically, you will create one Ad Unit per type of ad you&rsquo;d like to display in an app. For example, if you want to have a banner ad on one screen and a native ad in another, you&rsquo;d create an Ad Unit for each type. You can create a new &ldquo;...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Generating Ad Unit Code for Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/generating-ad-unit-code-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[From the Ad Unit page, you can pull the ad unit code by clicking &ldquo;Code Integration&rdquo;. Once all your ad units have been created, you can follow our technical guide to begin integration of the SDK. Documentation can be found here.&nbsp; &nbsp;]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The MoPub reporting tool can be found here or by clicking &lsquo;Reports&rsquo; under Your Account. &nbsp; Reports can be broken down using up to three different type of paramaters &nbsp; Please note that data for yesterday becomes available at 12:00PM Pacific Time &nbsp; You can...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Integrating 3rd Party Networks</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/integrating-3rd-party-networks</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Please follow links to our GitHub wiki for instructions on integrating third party networks such as AdMob, iAd and Millennial. iOS:&nbsp;https://github.com/mopub/mopub-ios-sdk/wiki#integrating-with-third-party-networks Android: https://github.com/mopub/mopub-android-sdk/wiki#integrating-with-...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Forecasting for Direct Ads</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/forecasting-direct-ads</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Overview of Forecasting MoPub&rsquo;s Forecasting feature allows you to quickly evaluate available impressions based on the inventory that&rsquo;s already been booked and sold. &nbsp;As shown below, Forecasting allows you to visualize available inventory, and see the value of each Guaranteed Line...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>How to Integrate the MoPub Native Ads SDK</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/how-integrate-mopub-native-ads-sdk</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Marketplace Access Publishers who are not approved will not be able to target their ad units at Marketplace and will see the UI below: &nbsp; To get access to Marketplace, please email nativeads@twitter.com to get your publisher approved. ​Downloading the SDK Publishers can download the SDK...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Click to Call Line Item</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/click-call-line-item</link>
   <description><![CDATA[If you you want an ad to dial a phone number then you will need to format that the click URL as such tel://55555555555. This will call the number when you click on the ad.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Integer Priority Levels</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/integer-priority-levels</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Integer Priority Levels enables publishers to assign priority levels to line items in their waterfall independent of the Line Item Type.&nbsp;Line Item Type and Priority are now independent from each other. How are Line Items Prioritized Using Integer Priority Levels? You can now edit the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Linking Line Items Directly to In-App Purchases</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/linking-line-items-directly-app-purchases</link>
   <description><![CDATA[To have the click through of ads go to an in-app purchase, you&#39;ll need to set up a custom URI scheme. Once you do that, all you have to do is drop the custom URI into the click through URL field of the creative. Additional documentation on how to create a custom URI can be found here.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>MoPub Macros</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mopub-macros</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub supports the following macros for a publisher&rsquo;s 3rd party ad tags and trackers: &nbsp; Click URL (Unescaped): &nbsp;%%CLICK_URL_UNESC%%&nbsp; &nbsp; Click URL (Escaped): &nbsp;%%CLICK_URL_ESC%% &nbsp; Cache Buster (Generates a random number): %%CACHEBUSTER%% &nbsp; Ad...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Progress &amp; Pacing Indicator</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/progress-pacing-indicator</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The progress indicator is located inside the pillbox and displays delivery of the entire campaign impression goal &nbsp; The pacing indicator displays the current pace of the campaign and the expected final delivery for the campaign &nbsp; &nbsp;]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
