<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 04:45:03 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Content Filtering</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-content-filtering</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Publishers can customize the type of ads that are served in their apps and sites by using the Content Filtering controls. &nbsp;Publishers can set the filtering level from Strict, Moderate, Low and No Filtering. &nbsp;Lowering the content filtering usually results in stronger fill and higher CPMs....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Blocking Specific Creatives</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/blocking-specific-creatives</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Individual creatives can be blocked on the ‘Creative Review’ Tab under the ‘Marketplace’ Tab. Check the specific creative you want to block and click the ‘Block/Unblock’ button. A drop down will show with the options Block Creative ID, Block Advertiser URL, Unblock Creative ID...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Ad Serving Sequence and CPM Values</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ad-serving-sequence-and-cpm-values</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Change CPMs and re-order the “waterfall” for a specific ad unit using the ‘Quick Edit’ function in the MoPub Dashboard tab. The ad unit waterfall is the sequence in which network ad sources are requested to fill each impression for a particular ad unit ID from within an application. Procedure:...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Mobile Web Ad Network Support</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mobile-web-ad-network-support</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Please note that Mobile Web does not support any Native Networks]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>LifeStreet Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/lifestreet-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Ad network revenue reporting allows you to view important metrics from your networks directly in MoPub. Learn more about ad network revenue reporting here. In order to set up ad network revenue reporting for LifeStreet, you will need to enter your LifeStreet username, password, and set your...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>JumpTap Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/jumptap-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Ad network revenue reporting allows you to view important metrics from your networks directly in MoPub. Learn more about ad network revenue reporting here. In order to set up ad network revenue reporting for Jumptap, you will need to enter your Jumptap username, password, and set your...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Issues with AdMob &amp; Proguard</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/issues-admob-proguard</link>
   <description><![CDATA[&nbsp; If you are using Proguard and the Admob the adapter is included but the AdMob SDK is getting stripped out, then when a call is made to that ad network, an application error will occur. &nbsp; In your configuration file of proguard (proguard.cfg), simply add this line: # AdMob Support -keep...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>InMobi Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/inmobi-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[We&rsquo;ve recently updated revenue reporting for InMobi to reflect InMobi&rsquo;s latest API. &nbsp;If you previously set up MoPub revenue reporting for InMobi, you need to contact InMobi and update your InMobi information on MoPub to ensure your reports continue to work. Important Notes:...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Create and Manage a Segment (Ad Networks)</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/create-and-manage-segment-ad-networks</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Segments Overview MoPub’s network management interface allows you to group your inventory into “segments”. A “segment” is a slice of your inventory with specific apps or ad units that can be targeted to specific countries and networks. It is a combination of three variables...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Chartboost Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/chartboost-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[In order to set up revenue reporting for Chartboost, you need to first set up Chartboost as a network. Directions to set up Chartboost. In order to set up Chartboost for revenue reporting, you will need to enter in your Chartboost User ID and Chartboost User Signature into the MoPub UI....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Chartboost Network Setup</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/chartboost-network-setup</link>
   <description><![CDATA[In order to set up Chartboost, you will need the most recent MoPub SDKs for iOS and Android. iOS: https://github.com/mopub/mopub-ios-sdk/ Android: https://github.com/mopub/mopub-android-sdk/ 1. You will first need to integrate the Chartboost SDK and Chartboost supporting...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Ad Networks FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ad-networks-faq</link>
   <description><![CDATA[What networks does MoPub support? MoPub supports dozens of the most popular ad networks via server-to-server connections. For a list of standard supported networks, visit here.&nbsp;In addition to these networks, you can set up any network on MoPub via a &quot;Custom Event&quot;.&nbsp;These...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>What is an Order &amp; Line Item?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/what-order-line-item</link>
   <description><![CDATA[In order to monetize your app with MoPub, you will need to set up orders and line items. In this section you will find more information on orders and line items. An Order is a a group of related Line Items, which are also known as campaigns. Line items are campaigns that have different...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>MoPub Technical Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mopub-technical-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Here you can find more information on how to work with various networks by creating Custom Event classes. You will also find technical integration and support guides. If you have a specific issue that is not addressed here, please feel free to post a topic in our Discussion Forum or contact...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Editing a Line Item</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/editing-line-item</link>
   <description><![CDATA[This page allows you to take a detailed look at a specific Line Item.&nbsp; &nbsp; The overall Line Item can be edited by clicking &lsquo;Edit Line Item&rsquo;. &nbsp; Line Items can be paused, resumed, or archived. &nbsp; On this page, you can add creative by clicking on the &ldquo;...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>MRAID Vendor Tag Certification Process</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mraid-vendor-tag-certification-process</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub MRAID Vendor Certification Process Guiding Principles: The MoPub SDK is built to be fully compliant with the IAB MRAID v1.0 specification Overview: Pre-Certification Questionnaire Tag Setup in MoPub UI MRAID Vendor Self Test MRAID Vendor Impression Test DSP Reporting Test...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Huntmads Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/huntmads-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Ad network revenue reporting allows you to view important metrics from your networks directly in MoPub. Learn more about ad network revenue reporting here. In order to set up ad network revenue reporting for Huntmads, you will need to enter your Huntmads API Token on the network setup...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter | MoPub Server-to-Server API Technical Specifications 1.0</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/twitter-mopub-server-server-api-technical-specifications-10</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Overview The MoPub Server-to-Server API makes it easier for ad networks and demand partners to connect with the MoPub platform outside of SDK libraries. To integrate with MoPub through the Server-to-Server API, follow the integration approval process and technical specifications...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Ad Network Best Practices</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ad-network-best-practices</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Locking down iAD Ad Unit Sizes If the application is a universal application, there are some standard integration steps to help with resizing of the ad units, particularly when trying to lock down iAd ad sizes. By following the steps and using the code snippet below, you have...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Setting Up MoPub Mobile Web Tags</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/setting-mopub-mobile-web-tags</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub supports a simple Javascript tag to integrate our ad serving technology into your mobile websites. Simply include the following tags, customized with your ad unit ID and creative size. Details Paste the following code snippet into your mobile webpage where you'd like to see ads appear:...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
