<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2014 04:45:02 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>Summary Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/summary-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Summary Card can be used for many kinds of web content, from blog posts and news articles, to products and restaurants. The screenshot below shows the expanded Tweet view for a New York Times article: Web Mobile...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Things Every Developer Should Know</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/things-every-developer-should-know</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Tweet IDs are enormous and break Javascript Use the id_str field instead of id whenever present to stay safe. Your web browser/Javascript interpreter/JSON consumer may munge our large integer-based ids which is why it's recommended to use the string representation. See Twitter IDs, JSON and...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Embedded Tweets</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/embedded-tweets</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Overview Embedded Tweets make it possible for you take any Tweet and embed it directly in to the content of your article or website. Tweets display with expanded media like photos, videos, and article summaries, and also include real-time retweet and favorite counts. When...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter公認製品プログラム</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/ja/programs/twitter-certified-products</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Twitter公認製品プログラムとはTwitterのエコシステムパートナーの中から日本市場の各業界ニーズに応え、ビジネスの課題解決にベストなソリューションとして特に優れているものを認定するプログラムです。 プログラムメンバーがTwitterのAPIやデータをフルに活用し、企業のさらなる発展を支援する製品やサービスを提供できるよう継続的にサポートしていきます。 各製品の詳細は公認製品リストよりご覧ください...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Crimson Hexagon</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/ja/programs/twitter-certified-products/crimson-hexagon</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 @BrainPad_PRさんをフォロー !function(d,s,id){var js,fjs=d.getElementsByTagName(s)[0],p=/^http:/.test(d.location)?'http':'https';if(!d.getElementById(id)){js=d.createElement(s);js.id=id;js.src=p+'://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js';fjs.parentNode.insertBefore(js,fjs);}}(document, '...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Calendar of API changes</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/calendar</link>
   <description><![CDATA[This page lists important upcoming dates for consumers of Twitter's APIs. The dates listed will be as specific as possible, but may not be exact for various reasons. Please continue to follow @twitterapi and the Twitter developer blog for announcements about the platform. Upcoming changes...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>App Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/app-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[App Card is a great way to better represent mobile applications on Twitter and to drive installs. We designed the App Card to allow for a name, description and icon, and also to highlight attributes such as the rating and the price. This will require adding some new markup tags to your pages,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Error Codes &amp; Responses</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/error-codes-responses</link>
   <description><![CDATA[HTTP Status Codes The Twitter API attempts to return appropriate HTTP status codes for every request. It is possible to suppress response codes for the REST API. Code Text Description 200 OK Success...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST lists/members/create</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/lists/members/create</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Add a member to a list. The authenticated user must own the list to be able to add members to it. Note that lists cannot have more than 5,000 members.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Summary Card with Large Image</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/large-image-summary-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[In addition to our regular Summary Card, we also have a format that allows you to feature a larger image above the title and description of the Card. The regular Summary Card features a thumbnail image in the upper right hand corner of the Card, but if you want to more prominently feature your...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter Cards</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Introduction Twitter Cards make it possible for you to attach media experiences to Tweets that link to your content. Simply add a few lines of HTML to your webpages, and users who Tweet links to your content will have a "card" added to the Tweet that’s visible to all of their followers....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>GET friendships/lookup</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/get/friendships/lookup</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Returns the relationships of the authenticating user to the comma-separated list of up to 100 screen_names or user_ids provided. Values for connections can be: following, following_requested, followed_by, none, blocking.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>GET lists/show</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1/get/lists/show</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Returns the specified list. Private lists will only be shown if the authenticated user owns the specified list.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Useful Links We Found</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/misc/useful-articles</link>
   <description><![CDATA[On using API v1.1 Using API v1.1 with the SignPost library for Scala or Java Streaming data from Twitter using the 1.1 Search API On OAuth Apigee's OAuth: the Big Picture Using OAuth for Twitter Authentication on the BlackBerry PlayBook Using Twitter API with LIFT, Scala, and...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Connecting to Twitter API using SSL</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/security/using-ssl</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Currently, only SSL connections are allowed in Twitter API endpoints. Communicating over SSL preserves user privacy by protecting information between the user and the Twitter API as it travels across the public Internet. Using OAuth isn't enough While OAuth is mandated and protects the user...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter Certified Products Program</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/programs/twitter-certified-products</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 The Twitter Certified program identifies the best products and services that help businesses thrive on Twitter. The Twitter Certified program consists of two data resellers &mdash; licensed to syndicate Tweet content &mdash; and a constantly growing list of the leading solutions from...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Certified Products</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/programs/twitter-certified-products/products</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Certified Products Product Description Badge Adobe Social Adobe Social connects the dots between social interactions and business results, enabling marketers to demonstrate social impact at every stage of the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter Certified Products Requirements</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/programs/twitter-certified-products/requirements</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The terms below are requirements for all products in the Twitter Certified Products Program. Current and potential partners must fully adhere to these requirements for certification. We encourage you to audit your product against all of these terms before applying to the Twitter Certified...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Application-only authentication</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/auth/application-only-auth</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Overview Twitter offers applications the ability to issue authenticated requests on behalf of the application itself (as opposed to on behalf of a specific user). Twitter's implementation is based on the Client Credentials Grant flow of the OAuth 2 specification. Note that OAuth 1.0a is still...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Player Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/player-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 The Player Card type requires special approval, and is not available for immediate approval at this time. The Player Card is for streaming media experiences such as audio, video, or slideshows, and allows you to present your content inside of an iframe within the Tweet....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
