<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 20:15:02 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>GET statuses/lookup</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/get/statuses/lookup</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Returns fully-hydrated tweet objects for up to 100 tweets per request, as specified by comma-separated values passed to the id parameter. This method is especially useful to get the details (hydrate) a collection of Tweet IDs. GET statuses/show/:id is used to retrieve a single tweet object.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Cards Troubleshooting Guide</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/troubleshooting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 We created this troubleshooting guide to help you identify and resolve commonly encountered issues during Cards development. We've tried to make this guide as useful and comprehensive as possible. If there's something wrong, or you feel something should be added, please reach out...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter Cards</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Introduction Twitter Cards make it possible for you to attach media experiences to Tweets that link to your content. Simply add a few lines of HTML to your webpages, and users who Tweet links to your content will have a "card" added to the Tweet that’s visible to all of their...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST blocks/create</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/blocks/create</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Blocks the specified user from following the authenticating user. In addition the blocked user will not show in the authenticating users mentions or timeline (unless retweeted by another user). If a follow or friend relationship exists it is destroyed.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>User Profile Images and Banners</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/user-profile-images-and-banners</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Profile Images Profile images (or avatars) are an important component of a Twitter account's expression of identity. To upload an avatar on behalf of a user, use POST account/update_profile_image. Alternative image sizes for user profile images You can obtain a user's most recent profile image,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST account/update_profile_banner</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/account/update_profile_banner</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Uploads a profile banner on behalf of the authenticating user. For best results, upload an]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Error Codes &amp; Responses</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/error-codes-responses</link>
   <description><![CDATA[HTTP Status Codes The Twitter API attempts to return appropriate HTTP status codes for every request. It is possible to suppress response codes for the REST API. Code Text Description 200 OK Success...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST account/update_profile_image</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/account/update_profile_image</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Updates the authenticating user's profile image. Note that this method expects raw multipart data, not a URL to an image. This method asynchronously processes the uploaded file before updating the user's profile image URL. You can either update your local cache the next time you request the user's...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>GET users/profile_banner</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/get/users/profile_banner</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Returns a map of the available size variations of the specified user's profile banner. If the user has not uploaded a profile banner, a HTTP 404 will be served instead. This method can be used instead of string manipulation on the profile_banner_url returned in user objects as described in User...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitterカード</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/ja/docs/cards</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 紹介 Twitterカードであなたのサイトへのリンクが入っているツイートにメディアを添付できます。あなたのウェブ・ページにHTMLを数行入れるだけで、どのユーザーもあなたのサイトへのリンクをツイートすると、そのツイートを見るすべてのフォロワーがカードを見られます。 カードであなたのツイートに対するエンゲージメント促進 ツイートにつけられるカードの種類は7種あります。各種類がtwitter.comでもでもTwitterのモバイル・クライアントでも綺麗に表示されます： Summary Card：標準のカードです。タイトル...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Playerカード</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/ja/docs/cards/types/player-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Playerカードを使用できる前に、特別な審査が必要です。 Playerカードは音声や動画、スライドショーを視聴できるカードです。コンテンツがツイート内のiframeの中に表示されます。PhotoやSummaryカードと異なり、コンテンツ配信に関する全てをデベロッパー側で管理する必要があり、下記の全てのTwitterアプリケーションで動作するよう実装しなければなりません。 twitter.com と mobile.twitter.com Twitter for iPhone Twitter for Android...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>トラブルシューティング＆FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/ja/docs/cards/troubleshooting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Twitterカードの設定に関して、よくある疑問やトラブルをまとめました。 なるべくすべての問題を網羅するよう心掛けておりますが、もし内容に誤りがあったり、他にも疑問がある場合は、 Twitter Card Discussion にてお気軽にお問い合せください。 カード検証ツールに関する問題 "exceeded 15.seconds to pink-floyd while waiting for a response for the request, including retries (...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>アプリケーション・インストールとディープ・リンク</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/ja/docs/cards/app-installs-and-deep-linking</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 紹介 新しいTwitterカードでは、インストールされていないネイティブ・アプリケーションをカードからインストールしたり、インストールされているネイティブ・アプリケーションへのディープ・リンクを設定できます。どのカードの種類でもアプリケーション・インストールとディープ・リンクを使用できます。以下に説明されている通り、必要なのはカード情報にメタタグを追加するだけです。 アプリケーション・インストール このタグを追加すれば、...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Calendar of API changes</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/calendar</link>
   <description><![CDATA[This page lists important upcoming dates for consumers of Twitter's APIs. The dates listed will be as specific as possible, but may not be exact for various reasons. Please continue to follow @twitterapi and the Twitter developer blog for announcements about the platform. Upcoming changes...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST statuses/update_with_media</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/statuses/update_with_media</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Updates the authenticating user's current status and attaches media for upload. In other words, it creates a Tweet with a picture attached. Unlike POST statuses/update, this method expects raw multipart data. Your POST request's Content-Type should be set to multipart/form-data with the media[]...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Where do I manage my Twitter applications?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/faq/#25871</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Manage your Twitter applications on https://apps.twitter.com by signing in with your Twitter account.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>What happened to application management on dev.twitter.com?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/faq/#25872</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Application management has moved to https://apps.twitter.com/.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Player Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/player-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 The Player Card type requires special approval, and is not available for immediate approval at this time. The Player Card is for streaming media experiences such as audio, video, or slideshows, and allows you to present your content inside of an iframe within the Tweet....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Gallery Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/gallery-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Gallery Card allows you to represent collections of photos within a Tweet. This Card type is designed to let the user know that there's more than just a single image at the URL shared, but rather a gallery of related images. You can specify up to 4 different images to show in the gallery...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Summary Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/summary-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The Summary Card can be used for many kinds of web content, from blog posts and news articles, to products and restaurants. The screenshot below shows the expanded Tweet view for a New York Times article: Web Mobile...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
