<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 15:15:02 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>Embedded Timelines</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/embedded-timelines</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Overview Embeddable timelines make it easy to syndicate any public Twitter timeline to your website with one line of code. Create an embedded timeline from your widgets settings page on twitter.com, or choose “Embed this…” from the options menu on profile, search and collection...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>iAd Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/iad-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub offers ad network revenue reporting for ad networks that offer a third party API to provide you with more accurate ad performance data.&nbsp; In order to set up ad network revenue reporting for iAd, you will need to enter your iTunes Connect username and password onto your iAd Network...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>GET statuses/lookup</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/get/statuses/lookup</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Returns fully-hydrated tweet objects for up to 100 tweets per request, as specified by comma-separated values passed to the id parameter. This method is especially useful to get the details (hydrate) a collection of Tweet IDs. GET statuses/show/:id is used to retrieve a single tweet object.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Huntmads Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/huntmads-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Ad network revenue reporting allows you to view important metrics from your networks directly in MoPub. Learn more about ad network revenue reporting here. In order to set up ad network revenue reporting for Huntmads, you will need to enter your Huntmads API Token&nbsp;&nbsp;on the network setup...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Issues with AdMob &amp; Proguard</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/issues-admob-proguard</link>
   <description><![CDATA[&nbsp; If you are using Proguard and the Admob the adapter is included but the AdMob SDK is getting stripped out, then when a call is made to that ad network, an application error will occur. &nbsp; In your configuration file of proguard (proguard.cfg), simply add this line: &nbsp; # AdMob...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Orders &amp; Line Items FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/orders-line-items-faq</link>
   <description><![CDATA[My line item is currently paused and I would like to set it live. When I do so, the line item remains in the paused state.What is going on? Please check the status of the order to which the line item belongs, and ensure that the order is set live. The order level supersedes the line...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Chartboost Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/chartboost-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[In order to set up revenue reporting for Chartboost, you need to first set up Chartboost as a network. Directions to set up Chartboost. In order to set up Chartboost for revenue reporting, you will need to enter in your Chartboost User ID and Chartboost User Signature into the MoPub UI. The User...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Chartboost Network Setup</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/chartboost-network-setup</link>
   <description><![CDATA[In order to set up Chartboost, you will need the most recent MoPub SDKs for iOS and Android. iOS: https://github.com/mopub/mopub-ios-sdk/ Android: https://github.com/mopub/mopub-android-sdk/ 1. You will first need to integrate the Chartboost SDK and Chartboost supporting files for ad serving to...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Ad Network Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ad-network-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub allows you to view your ad network revenue, impression, and click data, all in one place. From the MoPub interface you can get a snapshot of how your ad networks have been performing, allowing you to manage and optimize your revenue more efficiently. Sounds great, how do I get started? To...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Setting Up Ad Networks</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/setting-ad-networks</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub supports dozens of the most popular ad networks via server-to-server connections. For a list of standard supported networks, visit here. In addition to these networks, you can set up any network on MoPub via a &quot;Custom Event&quot;. These networks are referred to as a &quot;Custom...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>JumpTap Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/jumptap-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Ad network revenue reporting allows you to view important metrics from your networks directly in MoPub. Learn more about ad network revenue reporting here. In order to set up ad network revenue reporting for Jumptap, you will need to enter your Jumptap username, password, and set your Jumptap Site...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>LifeStreet Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/lifestreet-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Ad network revenue reporting allows you to view important metrics from your networks directly in MoPub. Learn more about ad network revenue reporting here. In order to set up ad network revenue reporting for LifeStreet, you will need to enter your LifeStreet username, password, and set your...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Self-Testing Your Creatives with the MoPub SDK and SimpleAdsDemo Sample App</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/self-testing-your-creatives-mopub-sdk-and-simpleadsdemo-sample-app</link>
   <description><![CDATA[This tutorial is a step-by-step guide that shows you how to self-test your creatives using the SimpleAds Demo app. Self Testing with the MoPub SDK and Simple Ads Demo App What: SimpleAds Demo is a mobile application for iOS and Android that demonstrates how live tags would render/behave on MoPub...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>IAB Categorization with Examples</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/iab-categorization-examples</link>
   <description><![CDATA[IAB Categorization with Examples IAB Category Name Examples IAB1 Arts & Entertainment IAB1-1 Books &amp; Literature...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Mojiva Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mojiva-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Ad network revenue reporting allows you to view important metrics from your networks directly in MoPub. Learn more about ad network revenue reporting&nbsp;here. In order to set up ad network revenue reporting for Mojiva, you will need to enter your private key&nbsp;on the networks set up page....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Refresh Rates</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/refresh-rates</link>
   <description><![CDATA[When you create an ad unit, you will need to set the refresh rate. The refresh rate is the number of seconds until the next ad unit displays. For example, if you set a refresh rate of 30 seconds, the second ad unit will display 30 seconds later...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>MRAID Vendor Tag Certification Process</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mraid-vendor-tag-certification-process</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub MRAID Vendor Certification Process Guiding Principles: The MoPub SDK is built to be fully compliant with the IAB MRAID v1.0 specification Overview: Pre-Certification Questionnaire Setup Vendor Self Test Vendor impression test Reporting test Scale Test Best Practices...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>GET help/languages</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/get/help/languages</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Returns the list of languages supported by Twitter along with the language code supported by Twitter. The language code may be formatted as ISO 639-1 alpha-2 (en), ISO 639-3 alpha-3 (msa), or ISO 639-1 alpha-2 combined with an ISO 3166-1 alpha-2 localization (zh-tw).]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Burstly Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/burstly-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Burstly SDK Passing IFA and Android ID values positively affects MoPub Marketplace performance. The following platform versions are certified to work correctly with MoPub Marketplace: iOS: Burstly SDK version 1.35+ required to pass IFA. Update Burstly SDK accordingly before...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>MoPub Dashboard FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mopub-dashboard-faq</link>
   <description><![CDATA[What is the MoPub Dashboard? The MoPub Dashboard enables you to see your entire monetization strategy on a single screen. The Dashboard offers a single, comprehensive view of all your app revenue data &mdash; including ad networks, MoPub Marketplace, and direct campaigns. How do I access the new...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
