<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 09:30:03 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>Creating Orders &amp; Line Items</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/creating-orders-line-items</link>
   <description><![CDATA[&nbsp; Clicking on &#39;Add a new Order&#39; will direct you to the Order &amp; Line Item page. Follow the steps below to create a new Order &amp; Line Item. &nbsp; Name your Order, drop in the Advertiser, and a short description &nbsp; You will then create your first Line Item for this...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>What is an Order &amp; Line Item?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/what-order-line-item</link>
   <description><![CDATA[An Order is a a group of related Line Items, which are also known as campaigns. &nbsp;Line items are campaigns that have different targeting. &nbsp;For example, you receive a Coca-Cola Order for a 728x90 United States Campaign, a 320x50 UK campaign, and a 300x250 United States and UK campaign....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>DFP Integration: Passing Key Values</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/dfp-integration-passing-key-values</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Passing Custom Key Values Add request parameters in the form $dfp_request_parameter DFP Support Links DFP API Integration Support Link AdMob SDK Support Link Macros are strings of text that the DoubleClick ad server replaces with other strings of text according to a set of rules...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>DFP Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/dfp-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[&nbsp; App Request url http://ads.mopub.com/m/ad?v=1&amp;tp=dfpm&amp;mr=1&amp;id=&lt;&lt;INSERT AD UNIT ID&gt;&gt; &nbsp; Mobile Web Request url http://ads.mopub.com/m/ad?v=1&amp;tp=dfpm&amp;mobile_web=1&amp;id=&lt;&lt;INSERT AD UNIT ID&gt;&gt; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>MRAID 2.0 Support</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mraid-20-support</link>
   <description><![CDATA[What is MRAID 2.0? MRAID (Mobile Rich-Media Ad Interface Definitions), is a framework for mobile advertisers and publishers that allows rich media ad creatives to run across all compliant devices and applications. It is a standard developed by the Internet Advertising Bureau (IAB) in late 2011....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Setting Up MoPub Mobile Web Tags</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/setting-mopub-mobile-web-tags</link>
   <description><![CDATA[See here for detailed instructions for implementing MoPub in Mobile Web: &nbsp; https://github.com/mopub/mopub-client/wiki/IntegrationHowToMobileWeb]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Android Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/android-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[See here for detailed instructions for integrating into Android applications: https://github.com/mopub/mopub-android-sdk/wiki/Getting-Started ​This includes documentation on conversion tracking, native SDK integration, custom events, keyword targeting, and passing location.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>iOS Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ios-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[See here for detailed instructions for integrating into iOS applications: https://github.com/mopub/mopub-ios-sdk/wiki This includes documentation on conversion tracking, native SDK integration,&nbsp;custom events, keyword targeting, and passing location. &nbsp;]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Blocking Specific Creatives</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/blocking-specific-creatives</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Individual creatives can be blocked on the &lsquo;Creative Review&rsquo; Tab under the &lsquo;Marketplace&rsquo; Tab. Check the specific creative you want to block and click the &lsquo;Block/Unblock&rsquo; button. A drop down will show with the options Block Creative ID, Block Advertiser URL,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Revenue Displayed in the Dashboard Different from Payment</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-revenue-displayed-dashboard-different-payment</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The revenues and other data displayed in the Marketplace dashboard may be different than the final payment. &nbsp;There are several reasons for this. &nbsp;The values shown in the dashboard are based on real-time data feed. &nbsp;At the end of the processing period, MoPub will look at the actual...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Payments</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-payments</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The MoPub Marketplace is designed never to lose money for the publisher. The bid received through the marketplace is compared with the eCPM you receive from the ad networks that you have manually set in MoPub. If the Marketplace bid eCPM is higher than the network, the Marketplace ad is delivered....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>How the Marketplace Competes with Ad Networks</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/how-marketplace-competes-ad-networks</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The MoPub Marketplace is designed never to lose money for the publisher. The bid received through the marketplace is compared with the eCPM you receive from the ad networks that you have manually set in MoPub. If the Marketplace bid eCPM is higher than the network, the Marketplace ad is delivered....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Price Floors</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-price-floors</link>
   <description><![CDATA[A price floor is the minimum price that you&rsquo;re willing to be paid for an impression from the Marketplace. For example, if you receive offers for ads that have a $0.50 CPM, but your price floor is $0.60 then those ads will not show. To have different price floors for different inventory, you...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Content Filtering</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-content-filtering</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Publishers can customize the type of ads that are served in their apps and sites by using the Content Filtering controls. &nbsp;Publishers can set the filtering level from Strict, Moderate, Low and No Filtering. &nbsp;Lowering the content filtering usually results in stronger fill and higher CPMs....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Blocking Advertisers on the Marketplace</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/blocking-advertisers-marketplace</link>
   <description><![CDATA[A blocklist allows you to block specific creative and advertisers from displaying ads on your apps. The blocklist can be found on the &ldquo;Settings&rdquo; tab within the Marketplace page. Particular advertisers can be blocked by adding the domain name (advertiser URL) of the advertiser to the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Turning the Marketplace On</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/turning-marketplace</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Go to the Marketplace tab &nbsp; Click the &ldquo;On&rdquo; switch &nbsp; Turn on all applications and ad units you want to participate in the Marketplace &mdash; There is no reason to have these deactivated &nbsp; Set your price floors&mdash;the minimum price that you&rsquo;re...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>MoPub Marketplace FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mopub-marketplace-faq</link>
   <description><![CDATA[What is the MoPub Marketplace? The MoPub Marketplace is a self-service, real-time bidding exchange for mobile apps and web sites. It enables publishers like you to plug in to more demand sources on the MoPub platform. You can think of a real-time bidding exchange like a real time auction where...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Ad Network Discrepancies</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ad-network-discrepancies</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The normal range for discrepancies are 5-10%. You should be concerned if discrepancies are 15%+. Below are the different circumstances as to why you may be experiencing discpreancies and the parties responsible for resolving. Custom Native Networks: These are networks that you are integrating the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Mobile Web Ad Network Support</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mobile-web-ad-network-support</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Please note that Mobile Web does not support any Native Networks]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Android Ad Network Support</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/android-ad-network-support</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The MoPub SDK can mediate any ad network through our server-to-server partners, adapters, and custom events capabilities. A full list of supported networks can be found here. We offer &#39;plug-and-play&#39; solutions for AdMob, iAd, Chartboost, and Millennial Media. To set these integrations up,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
