<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 09:15:03 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>MoPub Macros</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mopub-macros</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub supports the following macros for a publisher’s 3rd party ad tags and trackers: Click URL (Unescaped): &nbsp;%%CLICK_URL_UNESC%%&nbsp; Click URL (Escaped): &nbsp;%%CLICK_URL_ESC%%&nbsp; Cache Buster (Generates a random number): %%CACHEBUSTER%% Ad Group ID: %eaid! Creative ID: %ecid...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Managing Orders &amp; Line Items</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/managing-orders-line-items</link>
   <description><![CDATA[You can manage your Orders &amp; Line Items directly from the Orders page. Checking the box next to each of the Orders allows you to pause, resume, and archive. The Quick Jump button allows you to quickly jump between...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Integer Priority Levels</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/integer-priority-levels</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Integer Priority Levels enables publishers to assign priority levels to line items in their waterfall independent of the Line Item Type.&nbsp;Line Item Type and Priority are now independent from each other.How are Line Items Prioritized Using Integer Priority Levels? You can now edit the Priority...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>How to Create a Direct Native Ads Campaign</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/how-create-direct-native-ads-campaign</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Create an Ad Unit for your native ad &nbsp; Typically, you will create one Ad Unit per type of ad you&rsquo;d like to display in an app. For example, if you want to have a banner ad on one screen and a native ad in another, you&rsquo;d create an Ad Unit for each type. You can create a new &ldquo;...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Geo, Connectivity, and Device Targeting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/geo-connectivity-and-device-targeting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[When you create a new line item (and when editing line items) there are several targeting options available. Please note that you must always target an ad unit when creating a Line Item. &nbsp; County Targeting: Target your line item to a specific set of countries. By default, when the list is...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Editing an Order</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/editing-order</link>
   <description><![CDATA[This page allows you to edit the Order description, export Order details, and monitor overall performance. This page allows you to pause, resume, archive, or create a Line Item. The ‘Show...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Advanced Targeting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/advanced-targeting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[When you create a new line item (and when editing line items) you have the ability to use ‘Advanced Targeting’. &nbsp; Allocation Percentage: Under ‘Advanced Targeting’ you can allocate the percentage of requests you are sending to the Line Item, frequency cap, user target and keyword target....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Adding Creative to Line Items</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/adding-creative-line-items</link>
   <description><![CDATA[&nbsp; After you have created your guaranteed, promotional or backfill promotional Line Items, MoPub will ask you to add creative. &nbsp;If at any time you would like to add an additional creative, simply click on ‘Add a Creative’ icon on the right hand side.&nbsp; &nbsp; To add a creative, first...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Content Filtering</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-content-filtering</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Publishers can customize the type of ads that are served in their apps and sites by using the Content Filtering controls. &nbsp;Publishers can set the filtering level from Strict, Moderate, Low and No Filtering. &nbsp;Lowering the content filtering usually results in stronger fill and higher CPMs....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Blocking Specific Creatives</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/blocking-specific-creatives</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Individual creatives can be blocked on the ‘Creative Review’ Tab under the ‘Marketplace’ Tab. Check the specific creative you want to block and click the ‘Block/Unblock’ button. A drop down will show with the options Block Creative ID, Block Advertiser URL, Unblock Creative ID...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Ad Serving Sequence and CPM Values</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ad-serving-sequence-and-cpm-values</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Change CPMs and re-order the “waterfall” for a specific ad unit using the ‘Quick Edit’ function in the MoPub Dashboard tab. The ad unit waterfall is the sequence in which network ad sources are requested to fill each impression for a particular ad unit ID from within an application. Procedure:...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Mobile Web Ad Network Support</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mobile-web-ad-network-support</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Please note that Mobile Web does not support any Native Networks]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>LifeStreet Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/lifestreet-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Ad network revenue reporting allows you to view important metrics from your networks directly in MoPub. Learn more about ad network revenue reporting here. In order to set up ad network revenue reporting for LifeStreet, you will need to enter your LifeStreet username, password, and set your...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>JumpTap Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/jumptap-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Ad network revenue reporting allows you to view important metrics from your networks directly in MoPub. Learn more about ad network revenue reporting here. In order to set up ad network revenue reporting for Jumptap, you will need to enter your Jumptap username, password, and set your...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Issues with AdMob &amp; Proguard</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/issues-admob-proguard</link>
   <description><![CDATA[&nbsp; If you are using Proguard and the Admob the adapter is included but the AdMob SDK is getting stripped out, then when a call is made to that ad network, an application error will occur. &nbsp; In your configuration file of proguard (proguard.cfg), simply add this line: # AdMob Support -keep...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>InMobi Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/inmobi-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[We&rsquo;ve recently updated revenue reporting for InMobi to reflect InMobi&rsquo;s latest API. &nbsp;If you previously set up MoPub revenue reporting for InMobi, you need to contact InMobi and update your InMobi information on MoPub to ensure your reports continue to work. Important Notes:...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Create and Manage a Segment (Ad Networks)</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/create-and-manage-segment-ad-networks</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Segments Overview MoPub’s network management interface allows you to group your inventory into “segments”. A “segment” is a slice of your inventory with specific apps or ad units that can be targeted to specific countries and networks. It is a combination of three variables...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Chartboost Revenue Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/chartboost-revenue-reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[In order to set up revenue reporting for Chartboost, you need to first set up Chartboost as a network. Directions to set up Chartboost. In order to set up Chartboost for revenue reporting, you will need to enter in your Chartboost User ID and Chartboost User Signature into the MoPub UI....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Chartboost Network Setup</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/chartboost-network-setup</link>
   <description><![CDATA[In order to set up Chartboost, you will need the most recent MoPub SDKs for iOS and Android. iOS: https://github.com/mopub/mopub-ios-sdk/ Android: https://github.com/mopub/mopub-android-sdk/ 1. You will first need to integrate the Chartboost SDK and Chartboost supporting...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Ad Networks FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ad-networks-faq</link>
   <description><![CDATA[What networks does MoPub support? MoPub supports dozens of the most popular ad networks via server-to-server connections. For a list of standard supported networks, visit here.&nbsp;In addition to these networks, you can set up any network on MoPub via a &quot;Custom Event&quot;.&nbsp;These...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
