<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2014 00:45:02 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>Calendar of API changes</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/calendar</link>
   <description><![CDATA[This page lists important upcoming dates for consumers of Twitter's APIs. The dates listed will be as specific as possible, but may not be exact for various reasons. Please continue to follow @twitterapi and the Twitter developer blog for announcements about the platform. Upcoming changes...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Tweet Button</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/tweet-button</link>
   <description><![CDATA[By using the Tweet Button, you agree to the Developer Rules of the Road. Overview The Tweet Button is a small widget which allows users to easily share your website with their followers. This page is for developers and users who wish to build their own Tweet Buttons. If you are looking for a...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Set-up Twitter for Websites</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/tfw/set-up</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The easiest way to create a Twitter for Websites widget—a Tweet button, Follow button, embedded Tweet or timeline—is to use our configuration tools, then copy and paste the generated HTML code into the template for your site. Create a Tweet or Follow Button]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Web Intents</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/intents</link>
   <description><![CDATA[By using Web Intents, you agree to the Developer Rules of the Road. Make it easy to bring interactivity to Tweets that you display on the web. Web Intents provide popup-optimized flows for working with Tweets &amp; Twitter Users: Tweet, Reply, Retweet, Favorite, and Follow. They make it possible...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Things Every Developer Should Know</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/things-every-developer-should-know</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Tweet IDs are enormous and break Javascript Use the id_str field instead of id whenever present to stay safe. Your web browser/Javascript interpreter/JSON consumer may munge our large integer-based ids which is why it's recommended to use the string representation. See Twitter IDs, JSON and...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Streaming API request parameters</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/streaming-apis/parameters</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Use the following request parameters to define what data is returned by the Streaming API endpoints: delimited stall_warnings filter_level language follow track locations count with replies stringify_friend_ids delimited This parameter may be used on all streaming...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Player Card</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/player-card</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Video clips and audio streams have a special place on the Twitter platform thanks to the Player Card. By implementing a few HTML meta tags to your website and following the Twitter Rules of the Road, you can deliver your rich media to users across the globe. Player Card...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Player Card Approval Guide</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/types/player-card/approval-guide</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Thank you for your interest in using the Twitter Player Card. To help expedite the approval of your Card, it is useful to read the below fully and provide the appropriate information when prompted via e-mail. General Policy and Rules Most Common Issues Providing Us Additional Information...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Cards Troubleshooting Guide</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/troubleshooting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 We created this troubleshooting guide to help you identify and resolve commonly encountered issues during Cards development. We've tried to make this guide as useful and comprehensive as possible. If there's something wrong, or you feel something should be added, please reach out...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Sign up for Twitter&#039;s Developer Newsletter</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/sign-twitters-developer-newsletter</link>
   <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>GET statuses/show/:id</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/get/statuses/show/%3Aid</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Returns a single Tweet, specified by the id parameter. The Tweet's author will also be embedded within the tweet. See GET statuses/lookup for getting Tweets in bulk (up to 100 per call). See also Embeddable Timelines, Embeddable Tweets, and GET statuses/oembed for tools to render Tweets according...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>GET statuses/lookup</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/get/statuses/lookup</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Returns fully-hydrated tweet objects for up to 100 tweets per request, as specified by comma-separated values passed to the id parameter. This method is especially useful to get the details (hydrate) a collection of Tweet IDs. GET statuses/show/:id is used to retrieve a single tweet object.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter Cards</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 Introduction Twitter Cards make it possible for you to attach media experiences to Tweets that link to your content. Simply add a few lines of HTML to your webpages, and users who Tweet links to your content will have a "card" added to the Tweet that’s visible to all of their...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST blocks/create</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/blocks/create</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Blocks the specified user from following the authenticating user. In addition the blocked user will not show in the authenticating users mentions or timeline (unless retweeted by another user). If a follow or friend relationship exists it is destroyed.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>User Profile Images and Banners</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/user-profile-images-and-banners</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Profile Images Profile images (or avatars) are an important component of a Twitter account's expression of identity. To upload an avatar on behalf of a user, use POST account/update_profile_image. Alternative image sizes for user profile images You can obtain a user's most recent profile image,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST account/update_profile_banner</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/account/update_profile_banner</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Uploads a profile banner on behalf of the authenticating user. For best results, upload an]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Error Codes &amp; Responses</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/error-codes-responses</link>
   <description><![CDATA[HTTP Status Codes The Twitter API attempts to return appropriate HTTP status codes for every request. It is possible to suppress response codes for the REST API. Code Text Description 200 OK Success...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>POST account/update_profile_image</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/post/account/update_profile_image</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Updates the authenticating user's profile image. Note that this method expects raw multipart data, not a URL to an image. This method asynchronously processes the uploaded file before updating the user's profile image URL. You can either update your local cache the next time you request the user's...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>GET users/profile_banner</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/get/users/profile_banner</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Returns a map of the available size variations of the specified user's profile banner. If the user has not uploaded a profile banner, a HTTP 404 will be served instead. This method can be used instead of string manipulation on the profile_banner_url returned in user objects as described in User...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitterカード</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/ja/docs/cards</link>
   <description><![CDATA[English | 日本語 紹介 Twitterカードであなたのサイトへのリンクが入っているツイートにメディアを添付できます。あなたのウェブ・ページにHTMLを数行入れるだけで、どのユーザーもあなたのサイトへのリンクをツイートすると、そのツイートを見るすべてのフォロワーがカードを見られます。 カードであなたのツイートに対するエンゲージメント促進 ツイートにつけられるカードの種類は7種あります。各種類がtwitter.comでもでもTwitterのモバイル・クライアントでも綺麗に表示されます： Summary Card：標準のカードです。タイトル...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
