<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 20:30:02 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>Japanese Pages</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/ja</link>
   <description><![CDATA[アプリケーション・インストールとディープ・リンク Twitterカード トラブルシューティング＆FAQ Playerカード Twitter公認製品プログラム 開発者向けの表示要件 埋め込みタイムライン 埋め込みツイート ツイートボタン]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Technical Integration FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/technical-integration-faq</link>
   <description><![CDATA[I&rsquo;m testing my ad unit and nothing is happening. Why? At the moment, ad units that aren&#39;t receiving ad requests from live traffic get removed from our ad servers periodically. When the ad unit starts receiving traffic again, the information gets loaded on those machines and there&#39;s a...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>How To Integrate Facebook Audience Network Using Custom Events</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/how-integrate-facebook-audience-network-using-custom-events-0</link>
   <description><![CDATA[You can work with Facebook&#39;s Audience Network using Custom Events the same way you can with other ad network on MoPub. MoPub&#39;s pre-built Custom Event adapter makes this process even simpler. For more information on Custom Events, see Setting Up Ad Networks. Important Note: These Custom...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Server to Server Network Support</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/server-server-network-support</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub provides Server to Server integrations with the following networks: &nbsp; Jumptap &nbsp; InMobi &nbsp; MobFox &nbsp; Tapit &nbsp; Mojiva&nbsp; &nbsp; Huntmads &nbsp; This means that there is no additional development work required. Once you have created an account with a...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Ad Networks FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ad-networks-faq</link>
   <description><![CDATA[What networks does MoPub support? MoPub supports dozens of the most popular ad networks via server-to-server connections. For a list of standard supported networks, visit here.&nbsp;In addition to these networks, you can set up any network on MoPub via a &quot;Custom Event&quot;.&nbsp;These...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>MoPub Macros</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mopub-macros</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub supports the following macros for a publisher&rsquo;s 3rd party ad tags and trackers: &nbsp; Click URL (Unescaped): &nbsp;%%CLICK_URL_UNESC%%&nbsp; &nbsp; Click URL (Escaped): &nbsp;%%CLICK_URL_ESC%% &nbsp; Cache Buster (Generates a random number): %%CACHEBUSTER%% &nbsp; Ad...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>AdMarvel Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/admarvel-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[AdMarvel SDK When using the AdMarvel SDK, passing IFA and AndroidID can dramatically affect Marketplace performance. The versions below are certified to work correctly with Marketplace: iOS: AdMarvel SDK version 3.0.1 and higher is required to pass IDFA Android: All...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Checking the MoPub SDK Version</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/checking-mopub-sdk-version</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Checking the MoPub SDK Version As a best practice, we recommend that you update to the most recent version of the MoPub SDK every time you push an update to the Apple App Store or Google Play Store. To check the version of the SDK that is currently integrated in your...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Reporting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/reporting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The MoPub reporting tool can be found here or by clicking &lsquo;Reports&rsquo; under Your Account. &nbsp; Reports can be broken down using up to three different type of paramaters &nbsp; Please note that data for yesterday becomes available at 12:00PM Pacific Time &nbsp; You can...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Tweet Button parameter reference</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/tweet-button/reference</link>
   <description><![CDATA[A Tweet Button supports prepopulating share text, hashtags, and a Twitter account reference. Associate related Twitter accounts to drive followers. Tweet content parameters in_reply_to optional Status ID string of a parent Tweet such as a Tweet from your account (if applicable). Example...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Twitter | MoPub Server-to-Server API Technical Specifications 1.0</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/twitter-mopub-server-server-api-technical-specifications-10</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Overview The MoPub Server-to-Server API makes it easier for ad networks and demand partners to connect with the MoPub platform outside of SDK libraries. To integrate with MoPub through the Server-to-Server API, follow the integration approval process and technical specifications...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Generating Ad Unit Code for Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/generating-ad-unit-code-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[From the Ad Unit page, you can pull the ad unit code by clicking &ldquo;Code Integration&rdquo;. Once all your ad units have been created, you can follow our technical guide to begin integration of the SDK. &nbsp;]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Embedded Tweet parameter reference</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/embedded-tweets/reference</link>
   <description><![CDATA[An Embedded Tweet supports customization in data-* attributes and JavaScript factory functions. This reference document describes parameters used in all formats. Reference the oEmbed API to set these parameters as part of an HTML response for a Tweet ID or URL. Parameters id required The...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Create an Ad Unit</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/create-ad-unit</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Your application will require one or more Ad Units in order to show ads. From your Inventory tab, click “Add a New App” Select your platform choice in the Device Format section Select Ad Format type...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Add an Application to the Dashboard</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/add-application-dashboard</link>
   <description><![CDATA[To target ads to your application, add the application of interest into the MoPub dashboard. From your Inventory tab, click “Add a New App.” Platform: Select the OS you wish your application to target. Options: iOS, Android, Mobile Web...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Using Rich Media Creative</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/using-rich-media-creative</link>
   <description><![CDATA[To implement a rich media creative, select HTML at the Creative File Type, drop in the HTML rich media tag in the HTML body, and select MRAID ad when applicable. MoPub supports the following rich media vendors: Celtra, Flashtalking, and...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>DFP Integration: Passing Key Values</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/dfp-integration-passing-key-values</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Add request parameters in the form $dfp_request_parameter DFP Support Links DFP API Integration Support Link AdMob SDK Support Link Macros are strings of text that the DoubleClick ad server replaces with other strings of text according to a set of rules. Macros are case-sensitive...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>DFP Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/dfp-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[App Request URL http://ads.mopub.com/m/ad?v=1&amp;tp=dfpm&amp;mr=1&amp;id= &lt;&lt;INSERT AD UNIT ID&gt;&gt; Mobile Web Request URL http://ads.mopub.com/m/ad?v=1&amp;tp=dfpm&amp;mobile_web=1&amp;id= &lt;&lt;INSERT AD UNIT ID&gt;&gt; Create a MoPub Account...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Setting Up Ad Network IDs</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/setting-ad-network-ids</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Each of the ad networks will provide you a unique ID that you will enter next to your applications when creating a new network order. Below you will find where you can find each of those IDs for AdMob, AdSense, TapIt, InMobi, Jumptap, Millennial Media, Mojiva S2S &amp; MobFox...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Setting Up Ad Networks</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/setting-ad-networks</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub supports dozens of the most popular ad networks via server-to-server connections. For a list of standard supported networks, visit here. In addition to these networks, you can set up any network on MoPub via a "Custom Event". These networks are referred to as a "Custom Native Network...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
