<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 08:45:03 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Content Filtering</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-content-filtering</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Publishers can customize the type of ads that are served in their apps and sites by using the Content Filtering controls. &nbsp;Publishers can set the filtering level from Strict, Moderate, Low and No Filtering. &nbsp;Lowering the content filtering usually results in stronger fill and higher CPMs....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Blocking Advertisers on the Marketplace</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/blocking-advertisers-marketplace</link>
   <description><![CDATA[A blocklist allows you to block specific creative and advertisers from displaying ads on your apps. The blocklist can be found on the &ldquo;Settings&rdquo; tab within the Marketplace page. Particular advertisers can be blocked by adding the domain name (advertiser URL) of the advertiser to the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Turning the Marketplace On</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/turning-marketplace</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Go to the Marketplace tab &nbsp; Click the &ldquo;On&rdquo; switch &nbsp; Turn on all applications and ad units you want to participate in the Marketplace &mdash; There is no reason to have these deactivated &nbsp; Set your price floors&mdash;the minimum price that you&rsquo;re...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>MoPub Marketplace FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mopub-marketplace-faq</link>
   <description><![CDATA[What is the MoPub Marketplace? The MoPub Marketplace is a self-service, real-time bidding exchange for mobile apps and web sites. It enables publishers like you to plug in to more demand sources on the MoPub platform. You can think of a real-time bidding exchange like a real time auction where...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Ad Network Discrepancies</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ad-network-discrepancies</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The normal range for discrepancies are 5-10%. You should be concerned if discrepancies are 15%+. Below are the different circumstances as to why you may be experiencing discpreancies and the parties responsible for resolving. Custom Native Networks: These are networks that you are integrating the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Mobile Web Ad Network Support</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mobile-web-ad-network-support</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Please note that Mobile Web does not support any Native Networks]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Android Ad Network Support</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/android-ad-network-support</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The MoPub SDK can mediate any ad network through our server-to-server partners, adapters, and custom events capabilities. A full list of supported networks can be found here. We offer &#39;plug-and-play&#39; solutions for AdMob, iAd, Chartboost, and Millennial Media. To set these integrations up,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Resizing iAd Creative</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/resizing-iad-creative</link>
   <description><![CDATA[If the application is a universal application, there are some standard integration steps to help with resizing of the ad units, particularly when trying to lock down iAd ad sizes.&nbsp; &nbsp; By following the steps and using the code snippet below, you have the ability to lock down the native...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>iOS Ad Network Support</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ios-ad-network-support</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The MoPub SDK can mediate any ad network through our server-to-server partners, adapters, and custom events capabilities. A full list of supported networks can be found here. We offer &#39;plug-and-play&#39; solutions for AdMob, iAd, Chartboost, and Millennial Media. To set these integrations up,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Attempts vs. Requests</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/attempts-vs-requests</link>
   <description><![CDATA[When an ad is called, a request is logged within MoPub. An attempt is logged every time MoPub attempts an ad network. There can be several attempts made per request. For example, a request is made to MoPub. There are 3 ad networks that can fill this request. An attempt is made to each ad network...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Prioritizing Networks</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/prioritizing-networks</link>
   <description><![CDATA[MoPub&rsquo;s ad server prioritizes campaigns by eCPM, allowing us to give more space to the networks that are performing well at this very moment. The system works like a waterfall &ndash; it will attempt to show ads to the highest eCPM ad network first, and if it cannot fill, will trickle down to...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Setting Up Ad Network IDs</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/setting-ad-network-ids</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Each of the ad networks will provide you a unique ID that you will enter next to your applications when creating a new network order. Below you will find where you can find each of those IDs for AdMob, AdSense, TapIt, InMobi, Jumptap, Millennial Media, Mojiva S2S &amp; MobFox.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Ad Networks FAQ</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ad-networks-faq</link>
   <description><![CDATA[What networks does MoPub support? MoPub supports dozens of the most popular ad networks via server-to-server connections. For a list of standard supported networks, visit here.&nbsp;In addition to these networks, you can set up any network on MoPub via a &quot;Custom Event&quot;.&nbsp;These...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>IAB Attributes with Examples</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/iab-attributes-examples</link>
   <description><![CDATA[&nbsp; IAB Attributes with Examples The following list is derived from OpenRTB 2.1. The IAB taxonomy and standard are used for categorizing creatives. To assist you in better use of this taxonomy, MoPub has provided examples where applicable. For IAB Categories with Examples, see this article...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>IAB Categorization with Examples</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/iab-categorization-examples</link>
   <description><![CDATA[IAB Categorization with Examples The following list is derived from OpenRTB 2.1. The IAB taxonomy and standard is used for categorizing creatives. To assist you in better use of this taxonomy, MoPub has provided examples where applicable. For IAB Attributes with Examples, see this article...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>MoPub OpenRTB 2.1 Specification</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/mopub/openrtb-21-specification</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Updated August 4,2014 1. Overview MoPub RTB is a way for DSPs and advertisers to bid on each ad impression where the winning bid will pay the second-highest price in the auction.  This protocol is largely based on the OpenRTB 2.1 specification.   Note that our adaptation may require certain...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Cards Markup Tag Reference</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/cards/markup-reference</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The table in this section explains the OpenGraph fallback behavior for each Twitter tag. Overview of all Twitter Card Tags Property Card Value OpenGraph Fallback twitter:card all summary,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Mobile sign in flow</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mobile-sign-flow</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Mobile flow The UI flow for mobile web browsers works exactly like the Browser sign in flow, but is optimized for mobile browsers. Below are screenshots for the signed in, signed out, and redirect screens:]]></description>
   <pubDate></pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>GET geo/similar_places</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/api/1.1/get/geo/similar_places</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Locates places near the given coordinates which are similar in name.]]></description>
   <pubDate></pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
