<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</title>
  <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/recent</link>
  <description>Twitter API Recently Updated Documentation</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 10:00:02 +0200</pubDate>
  <generator>RouxRC</generator>
  <item>
   <title>Using Rich Media Creative</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/using-rich-media-creative</link>
   <description><![CDATA[&nbsp; To implement a rich media creative, select HTML at the Creative File Type, drop in the HTML rich media tag in the HTML body, and select MRAID ad when applicable. &nbsp; MoPub supports the following rich media vendors:&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;Celtra...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Setting Up Conversion Tracking</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/setting-conversion-tracking</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Conversion tracking is used to properly measure the effectiveness of cross-promotions and direct sold advertisements. &nbsp;Therefore, we recommend that publishers always implement conversion tracking. The conversion tracking network event only happens once-- a file is stored on device so that the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Centering Tags</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/centering-tags</link>
   <description><![CDATA[If you implement a tag, and the ad is not centering, you have the ability to center the tag. &nbsp;For example, if you created a Guaranteed campaign and implemented a 300x250 Javascript tag, but the ad is justified to the left, you should wrap the tag in center tags. &nbsp;This is done by including...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Adding Creative to Line Items</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/adding-creative-line-items</link>
   <description><![CDATA[&nbsp; After you have created your guaranteed, promotional or backfill promotional Line Items, MoPub will ask you to add creative. &nbsp;If at any time you would like to add an additional creative, simply click on &lsquo;Add a Creative&rsquo; icon on the right hand side.&nbsp; &nbsp; To add a...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Advanced Targeting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/advanced-targeting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[When you create a new line item (and when editing line items) you have the ability to use &lsquo;Advanced Targeting&rsquo;. &nbsp; Allocation Percentage: Under &lsquo;Advanced Targeting&rsquo; you can allocate the percentage of requests you are sending to the Line Item, frequency cap, user target...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Geo, Connectivity, and Device Targeting</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/geo-connectivity-and-device-targeting</link>
   <description><![CDATA[When you create a new line item (and when editing line items) there are several targeting options available. Please note that you must always target an ad unit when creating a Line Item. &nbsp; County Targeting: &nbsp; Target your line item to a specific set of countries. By default, when the...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Managing Orders &amp; Line Items</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/managing-orders-line-items</link>
   <description><![CDATA[&nbsp; You can manage your Orders &amp; Line Items directly from the Orders page. &nbsp; Checking the box next to each of the Orders allows you to pause, resume, and archive. &nbsp; The Quick Jump button allows you to quickly jump between different Orders and Line Items &nbsp;...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Creating Orders &amp; Line Items</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/creating-orders-line-items</link>
   <description><![CDATA[&nbsp; Clicking on &#39;Add a new Order&#39; will direct you to the Order &amp; Line Item page. Follow the steps below to create a new Order &amp; Line Item. &nbsp; Name your Order, drop in the Advertiser, and a short description &nbsp; You will then create your first Line Item for this...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>What is an Order &amp; Line Item?</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/what-order-line-item</link>
   <description><![CDATA[An Order is a a group of related Line Items, which are also known as campaigns. &nbsp;Line items are campaigns that have different targeting. &nbsp;For example, you receive a Coca-Cola Order for a 728x90 United States Campaign, a 320x50 UK campaign, and a 300x250 United States and UK campaign....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>DFP Integration: Passing Key Values</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/dfp-integration-passing-key-values</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Passing Custom Key Values Add request parameters in the form $dfp_request_parameter DFP Support Links DFP API Integration Support Link AdMob SDK Support Link Macros are strings of text that the DoubleClick ad server replaces with other strings of text according to a set of rules...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>DFP Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/dfp-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[&nbsp; App Request url http://ads.mopub.com/m/ad?v=1&amp;tp=dfpm&amp;mr=1&amp;id=&lt;&lt;INSERT AD UNIT ID&gt;&gt; &nbsp; Mobile Web Request url http://ads.mopub.com/m/ad?v=1&amp;tp=dfpm&amp;mobile_web=1&amp;id=&lt;&lt;INSERT AD UNIT ID&gt;&gt; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>MRAID 2.0 Support</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/mraid-20-support</link>
   <description><![CDATA[What is MRAID 2.0? MRAID (Mobile Rich-Media Ad Interface Definitions), is a framework for mobile advertisers and publishers that allows rich media ad creatives to run across all compliant devices and applications. It is a standard developed by the Internet Advertising Bureau (IAB) in late 2011....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Setting Up MoPub Mobile Web Tags</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/setting-mopub-mobile-web-tags</link>
   <description><![CDATA[See here for detailed instructions for implementing MoPub in Mobile Web: &nbsp; https://github.com/mopub/mopub-client/wiki/IntegrationHowToMobileWeb]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Android Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/android-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[See here for detailed instructions for integrating into Android applications: https://github.com/mopub/mopub-android-sdk/wiki/Getting-Started ​This includes documentation on conversion tracking, native SDK integration, custom events, keyword targeting, and passing location.]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>iOS Integration</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/ios-integration</link>
   <description><![CDATA[See here for detailed instructions for integrating into iOS applications: https://github.com/mopub/mopub-ios-sdk/wiki This includes documentation on conversion tracking, native SDK integration,&nbsp;custom events, keyword targeting, and passing location. &nbsp;]]></description>
   <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Blocking Specific Creatives</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/blocking-specific-creatives</link>
   <description><![CDATA[Individual creatives can be blocked on the &lsquo;Creative Review&rsquo; Tab under the &lsquo;Marketplace&rsquo; Tab. Check the specific creative you want to block and click the &lsquo;Block/Unblock&rsquo; button. A drop down will show with the options Block Creative ID, Block Advertiser URL,...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Revenue Displayed in the Dashboard Different from Payment</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-revenue-displayed-dashboard-different-payment</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The revenues and other data displayed in the Marketplace dashboard may be different than the final payment. &nbsp;There are several reasons for this. &nbsp;The values shown in the dashboard are based on real-time data feed. &nbsp;At the end of the processing period, MoPub will look at the actual...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Payments</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-payments</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The MoPub Marketplace is designed never to lose money for the publisher. The bid received through the marketplace is compared with the eCPM you receive from the ad networks that you have manually set in MoPub. If the Marketplace bid eCPM is higher than the network, the Marketplace ad is delivered....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>How the Marketplace Competes with Ad Networks</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/how-marketplace-competes-ad-networks</link>
   <description><![CDATA[The MoPub Marketplace is designed never to lose money for the publisher. The bid received through the marketplace is compared with the eCPM you receive from the ad networks that you have manually set in MoPub. If the Marketplace bid eCPM is higher than the network, the Marketplace ad is delivered....]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>Marketplace Price Floors</title>
   <link>https://dev.twitter.com/docs/marketplace-price-floors</link>
   <description><![CDATA[A price floor is the minimum price that you&rsquo;re willing to be paid for an impression from the Marketplace. For example, if you receive offers for ads that have a $0.50 CPM, but your price floor is $0.60 then those ads will not show. To have different price floors for different inventory, you...]]></description>
   <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
